raiikouu: yoo
raiikouu: waddup
awesomeo113: Wooo
raiikouu: lunch good?
ne3cross: Yo yo
eax_ebx: Привет.
Armitage9: its boss time
LiamS212: Sup cunt
benchai18: Hey Jorgè
nanodanger7: nanodanger7 subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 19 months, currently on a 19 month streak!
zinc_lord: yo
eaglesemanation: дарова
connord60: What’s up George? Big fan hope all is well
Mariosavitch: piss asmr
benchai18: No cock today Jorgè?
robotboy987: damn
geochill1: we seeing some driving simulations today?
robotboy987: Carla on Mac?
awesomeo113: Jorgé, the baddest takuache to ever live
geochill1: sweet
lambdaman0f: what are your thoughts on Haskell?
gyrojosh: Your such a boss
yodiggity4739: what are your thoughts on VISUAL BASIC
johan_ub: Gay
benchai18: U are a freak of nature
xteam159: There's no way after watching one of your podcast and I was about to go sleep and I get notified you are live BibleThump
awesomeo113: Ooowee nothing like some mukbang
chocolatechp: george! george!
shanumbra: do you watch porn ?
yodiggity4739: i think visual basic may be the best programming language of all
Alpasfly: do you think knowing how to solve dynamic programming and branch and bound problems is important?
zinc_lord: marinara vs alfredo?
Alpasfly: so what's the plan for today g-dawg?
gyrojosh: weird if you dont
cj1m: should I drop out?
ftt0717: The legend.
banditor: george, what do i need to eat to be as smart as you?
benchai18: Cock or coq?
chocolatechp: did you sprinkle cheese on it
shanumbra: fav category?
geochill1: Let's simulate transporting 20 tons of butter coast-to-coast
yodiggity4739: what if its rehab
ftt0717: But it tastes like crap.
robotboy987: dude imagine you drop food on your computer 😂
Halixness: water-cooling Mac by putting it on a plate with iced water?
Mariosavitch: no
yodiggity4739: yes
benchai18: @robotboy987 Ask him what kinda keyboard he uses. Just in case he drops food on it
yodiggity4739: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
Halixness: what if Catalina forces update while streaming lol
johan_ub: Hi. Everyone who is watching on commaai archive!!
ftt0717: DONT DO IT.
connord60: George I’m working on an app for place kickers in football any advice for getting the word out and some publicity
yunk3r: micro artisanal delivery
yodiggity4739: god i love butter transportation
connord60: As a college student
benchai18: George how big is your coq?
chocolatechp: do you only date other programmers?
shanumbra: is your gf a programmer ?
c9bd: what did i tune into
vidyogams: bruh
kornez: LUL
ftt0717: ........
awesomeo113: We live in a society
6majed: LUL
bubbychernicoff: @georgehotz how have you been enjoying san diego
gyrojosh: its go time
CaptCalifornia: @bubbychernicoff is he still there? isn't his company's office in SF?
yodiggity4739: i cannot follow along i lack the critical information
PhysoTronic: he is really working on comma ai or title is just Jebaited
Alpasfly: why mac and not linux?
bsx1123: Is it possible (in the future) to use openpilot on the Renault Zoe?
bubbychernicoff: @CaptCalifornia did they move back from SD to SF?
soeim: it was his company's idea to move him to san diego
banditor: how bout Raspbian?
Keyeh: i thought openpilot run on a car though
CaptCalifornia: @bubbychernicoff legit didnt know they moved my bad lol
tkrsh009: lets goo
twiggy_io: George who took over your body. You said you would never talk about it...
yodiggity4739: Pog
oMythra: you done any more hack the boxes?
CaptCalifornia: PepePls
awesomeo113: Yeah fuck Elon
gyrojosh: i see what they did there
chocolatechp: oh so this is like gta
ZemkeCWT: So, is it now allowed to talk about comma?
robotboy987: Carla is awesome
yodiggity4739: is that a picture of carla
PhysoTronic: are we gonna do meditation today too?
alreye: so carla is like a sex doll ?
ftt0717: “Yeaaahhh”
yodiggity4739: car LA
jay_al97: oh i saw one guy on YT training a model on this game
ssp3xx: I feel that
chocolatechp: afternoon 'coffee'
ssp3xx: morning coffe wrecks
unluckychickenn: unluckychickenn subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 3 months!
PhysoTronic: georgehotz all good until you start chewing that ice Kappa
bubbychernicoff: Would you recommend other Silicon Valleys moving to SD?
Keyeh: so i guess carla is a car simulator for Los Angeles? Kappa
dorkmo: Pride1
yunk3r: is carla mac only?
smurfd0: Gona openpilot Carla?
yodiggity4739: bob the builder
puffnfresh: puffnfresh subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 3 months! when we gonna use Coq to verify comma.ai?
geochill1: Does 0.7 support fingerprinting 2.0 or is that still being worked on
aymanpoquito: hellow
yodiggity4739: carla needs milk in the cereal
awesomeo113: I like my ice with starch
chocolatechp: i want to learn vim
chocolatechp: and be just like you george!
PhysoTronic: this is anti ice addiction stream, we dont talk about ice here LUL
xteam159: carla is my mom's name SeemsGood SeemsGood
yodiggity4739: chewing ice bad for teeth
banditor: You must be typing in a non mechanical keyboard
veomx: Hi George :) good to see you
benchai18: George TRUE or FALSE: Saurik is working on a comma ai substitute?
Kyoto_o: No :)
okeeeeeee: oh carla noice, recently i did something with carla and ROS
champ900: @georgehotz George how much do you code each day
th3_maj0r: yoyo boyz
chocolatechp: you eat like a pig
chocolatechp: oink oink
PhysoTronic: LUL
benchai18: Correct. It’s bullshit
geobitz: ikr got an orange lil nosie
th3_maj0r: did you buy the new mac pro george? don't you need 1.5TB of RAM?
yodiggity4739: oss
Kyoto_o: wash your mouth/nose before it goes on for too long :)
veomx: you have sauce on your nose
yodiggity4739: soss
Kyoto_o: he got the sauce literally KEKW
chair_78: you eat like there isn't a camera in front of you
samtheprogram: you changed the wrong os?
yodiggity4739: does anyone use TEXTEDIT.app
geobitz: u have sauce on your nose fool
Kyoto_o: it's quite pricey
geochill1: Have a timeline for complete fingerprinting 2.0?
Keyeh: isn't it like 50 grand
Abnico: new mac is to big
yodiggity4739: theres a new xbox
awesomeo113: I need 1.5 Tb of ram
tkrsh009: yes me too
champ900: @georgehotz why don't you use bash
benchai18: @yodiggity4739 Looks like a PC tho
Keyeh: i only need 256kb of memory :)
Abnico: why are u gay?
lightofhel1: !uptime
Abnico: zsh ftw
awesomeo113: All hail the cheese grater
benchai18: @yodiggity4739 I’m a lifelong Sony guy, but not gonna lie, their Hellblade 2 trailer makes me wanna get one
squiggly_nibba: Download item
squiggly_nibba: *iterm
my_curiosity: george, you beutiful person. why did you open source this project ...
yodiggity4739: tru
Abnico: iterm is trash
Keyeh: @my_curiosity i think he was going for an android kind of deal
yodiggity4739: what is scons
gyrojosh: pressing buttons
JesseSkinner: whats for supper
Kyoto_o: massaHmm
jagger_rsw: pthread_kill
samtheprogram: ^^^
dorkmo: mash the keyboard buttons = hacking
champ900: "hacking is about guessing" - George, 2019
veomx: George you like fettuccine?
benchai18: Jorgè u got a PO Box I can send a Hanukkah gift to? Totally appropriate.... not chocolate dicks or hazmat
gyrojosh: life itself is a scam
Julianhgg: greeting geo the boss
yodiggity4739: PogChamp
Keyeh: pretty cool
gyrojosh: SeemsGood
chocolatechp: 100 highway miles
yodiggity4739: i bet that video made elon feel sad :[
JesseSkinner: does your startup, i assume then, use openpilot?
Abnico: ordered a prius for christmas
zigzati: PauseChamp 100 miles
dorkmo: Corgo1
benchai18: I thought George does/did some work for Tesla?
deed02392: surely Tesla are still trying to raise money off the back of their progress?
Keyeh: tesla is a scam
samtheprogram: I don't know if I've ever seen George refactor
Abnico: tesla pre order
Keyeh: didn't you hear him
benchai18: @keyeh Cool thanks for the heads up
devm0d: Interview with Hacker 'Phineas Fisher' as a Puppet with Vice is pretty funny https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BpyCl1Qm6Xs
deed02392: I just joined
benchai18: @keyeh Nope.. I’m playing death stranding so I got distracted
yodiggity4739: wont the big companies use the ideas in openpilot for themselves
my_curiosity: I feel like this statement that high technology is generally a fucking scam is something that everyone in the industry knows deep inside, but is afraid to admit
zigzati: @yodiggity4739 ya xD
Keyeh: george you are so good coding C, why do you use python for everything?
devm0d: It's faster @Keyeh
vexedkiller0071: python has better libraries
devm0d: faster to develop that is
vexedkiller0071: faster
zigzati: @my_curiosity "in the industry"
vexedkiller0071: and ez
Keyeh: that's fair
eaglesemanation: is it possible to make devices with comma to communicate with other deviced?
champ900: George do you respect Elon
my_curiosity: Elon is probably the most successful scam artist in the history of humanity
devm0d: More than Trump?
warpoit: stay BLESSED bro.
benchai18: @yodiggity4739 Fair question. I was telling my past colleague that I love open source, and he goes “anyone who makes smtn cool and open sources it is an idiot and missing out millions n millions of $”. Mind u, he has nothing to do with tech industry. I think he heard an anecdote of a kid making something cool and getting it jacked cuz he opened it
Super_saiyan_3: how many word per min can u type homie?
ReDD_TV_: "basic" programming
deed02392: I don't believe he's a scammer. I genuinely believe he's a philanthropist
benchai18: @super_saiyan_3 Depends on his keyboard. Ask him which one he’s using
Yogohami: How is Elon a scammer ?
samtheprogram: @Super_saiyan_3 it depends how many symbols are in the test
gyrojosh: also is open source considered less secure?
theduckthough: no
ImJ4Gu4R: halo haloozzzz
Keyeh: quite the opposite
devm0d: Generally the opposite
devm0d: As anyone can audit it, open PR's, fix it
Biffingtonn: Never understood how people thought Elon was a scammer
eaglesemanation: I mean what if one car sees some dangerous situation, could it provide this information to other cars or something
JesseSkinner: @gyrojosh no.. we call the opposite "security through obscurity" which is not great
gyrojosh: sure, but works other way also
deed02392: I mean, there's a lag between when it's open sourced and when it's secure
theduckthough: how did your little adventure with the formal prover go?
deed02392: if you take a large private code base and open source it, you're gonna have a bad time
vloood: i mean hyperloop was a bad idea
deed02392: especially when you typically get more black hat Interest than white hat
benchai18: @deed02392 You are smart and I agree with u on Elon and sec and code
deed02392: vloood it's not a bad idea, any more than people thought starting an electric car company was a bad idea, or a private space venture
deed02392: aw thanks benchai18
Keyeh: didn't elon got in trouble with secutiry experts for hyperloop?
benchai18: @deed02392 ❤️
Keyeh: get*
vloood: @deed02392 no actually that is a bad idea that's not gonna work, that's why he pivoted to tunnels
deed02392: nah, the tunnels are for intra City transport
deed02392: hyperloop still makes sense for intercity
lightofhel1: why do we need openpilot on mac? @georgehotz
Abnico: are you ever going to make comma coin for token incentives?
Erciks: i did 4Head
Keyeh: for when apple start their car company
r3mote: Oh hi :)
Keyeh: Kappa
thundershots999: Anyone getting the $50k mac pro cheese grater?
deed02392: lolol
Abnico: amd cards only
deed02392: I could get one at work if they get it on the esxi HCL
zigzati: @thundershots999 plenty of folks will :)
samtheprogram: why only OS X < 10.12?
Abnico: cant do any rendering without cuda sad
champ900: open source is not self sustainable and that's why companies are moving away from it
aymanpoquito: @thundershots999 nah
Abnico: how are they moving away from it lol
benchai18: @champ900 Exblain please
Abnico: if anything they are encouraging it
theduckthough: patch script?
fmega: champ900 except they're not
abrahamstr: Hi George
Abnico: open source is the future
deed02392: my name is George too. this is fun
Abnico: all this tech is feature
yoyo_brobro: yoyo_brobro subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 8 months, currently on a 8 month streak!
oMythra: yea nobody is moving away from open source lol
Abnico: everything will be commoditized
JesseSkinner: 25 years ago shareware was hot and open source was super niche. now microsoft owns github
Abnico: meaning i can run twitter or facebook, the only thing of value is growth/network effect
deed02392: amen @jesseskinner
crimson_andre: alo
trippledrizzle: hello
lightofhel1: use if for imports?
deed02392: it's totally possible to make money out of open source
crimson_andre: what is open source
deed02392: you just take advantage of the open source aspect to rank up adoption
lightofhel1: or like this xD
JesseSkinner: you can charge money to support your open source project. you can launch a whole business around it like Gatsby
the_shining: What is he writing
Abnico: open source means open source
duzy: PogChamp
zigzati: @the_shining MrDestructoid 🚗
Keyeh: compiling Pog
deep_40k: @georgehotz How long did it take you to get this good?
samtheprogram: PogChamp
JesseSkinner: or run a hosted version like wordpress.com vs wordpress.org
the_shining: ok
chair_78: make the font larger
thismustbekirk: error: family of 5 terminated
lnter0: thats the trick
lightofhel1: LUL LUL LUL
samtheprogram: ouch
rektiw0w: hello mr twitch streamer
Abnico: been testing gatsby
Abnico: real nice, sad i found out about it later
crimson_andre: StoneLightning
thismustbekirk: what do you make with Gatsby?
the_shining: WutFace ResidentSleeper
HardDenmark: some much aggresion goes into pressing these keys kappa
anguscupcake: damn u got the vim skills
Abnico: lmao didnt know u like lorde
samtheprogram: @deep_40k his entire life
deed02392: should we listen to some Grimes? lol
crimson_andre: pepejammmmam
crimson_andre: tf are you writing
h4sb: lord e
TommyDGod: oh no, not billy eyelash
deed02392: ohh lordy
HardDenmark: isnt billie's shit written by her brother
oMythra: pepoDance
deed02392: ya ya ya I am lorde
tkrsh009: this used to be my alarm
tkrsh009: years ago
Abnico: yo i saw her at a chinese restaurant
JesseSkinner: lorde lorde lorde, i am lorde
knilecrack: what you doin brah?
deed02392: I think he's working on open pilot from a mac
ajd13c: song bro?
ajd13c: !sojng
ajd13c: !song
sadpoopz: lorde team
oMythra: mac shmac
deed02392: I guess the first step is getting it to build
the_shining: errors
eaglesemanation: !hack mainfraim
aymanpoquito: @ajd13c lorde team
Erichmoraga: Sell Mac > buy PC
deed02392: maybe George loves his new 16" mbp and wants to use it full time? :p
anguscupcake: I got a free mac and it's pretty nice actually
oMythra: all that new screen real estate
deed02392: Yea I got one with work and I do really like it
aymanpoquito: @anguscupcake yeah same bruh
Canuckles_: New mbp keyboard Kreygasm
oMythra: when you get one with work do you just max it out or what?
deed02392: I even bought an ipad now after being an android guy
deed02392: @omythra hells yea.
Abnico: who cares about tools
Abnico: just use anything pimps
oMythra: thats the life
samtheprogram: is he compiling it on mac os for carla dot org?
treestompztv: o/
Abnico: tribalism is for peasants
samtheprogram: because otherwise probably cross compiles anyway?
deed02392: although 'max out' = 16 GB RAM which is kinda lame. it's à 2017 model
theduckthough: what's preventing Cython to be cross platform? Wouldn't it only need a few abstractions?
topped123: george i decided to stop being an npc today and now im a main character
anguscupcake: tbh the thing I like most about macs is you can't waste time on video games
deed02392: haha
treestompztv: @anguscupcake LUL
deed02392: well I play worms Armageddon on it from a Windows vm
oMythra: solid points being made
deed02392: Also Apple arcade bro
deed02392: Guess it's gonna kill your productivity
Abnico: George, will comma coin ever come out? token incentives may be a good experiment in the future
Major_Spicy: @georgehotz I quit college to focus on other things (was studuying programming basically). Now that i feel like i still want to learn it, is taking online courser good enough still to learn well?
lidermaury: George please do christmas stream where you will be talking about keyboards while programming flappy bird
Vesh: george do u have tomato sauce around your mouth
anguscupcake: noooooo
raiikouu: Vesh ye he hate pasta
raiikouu: LUL
Vesh: lmao LUL
oMythra: its part of his look
Keyeh: @lidermaury hell yeah, with the santa hat
Vesh: i dig it
oMythra: last time he had sauce too LUL
aymanpoquito: @oMythra lol
Vesh: eating aint easy @oMythra
ZemkeCWT: Worms Armageddon, what’s your username on there?
deed02392: me? same as here :)
deed02392: do you still play?
deed02392: I'm a pretty good roper
IMMAPCGAMERD00D: IMMAPCGAMERD00D subscribed at Tier 1.
ZemkeCWT: I’m creator of CWT actually. http://cwtsite.com/
brickvo: thoughts on 50k mac LUL
deed02392: I know someone who just bought one
barretois: what do you think about software engineering
samtheprogram: they used to...
knilecrack: what's GELS?
deed02392: I mean, it's not terrible value for money if you want to use it for what it's made for
knilecrack: GLES*
ne3cross: You have openGL
samtheprogram: GLES = openGL ES
Keyeh: not sure i'm ready to give up a kidney to buy a mac LUL
deed02392: lol
deed02392: but you have two dude
knilecrack: @samtheprogram tlhx
ne3cross: look at Johntheripper for example
Keyeh: what if next iphone is 20k, then i'll have none
zigzati: @deed02392 not if i live off cheese balls
deed02392: hashcat has completely replaced jtr now come on
knilecrack: the problem is not in 50k mac, the problem is in 400 wheels
tkrsh009: or 1000 stand
TheRealShoks: what is he coding a python module?
deed02392: lol fair @zigzati . I just started a 7 day water fast today
knilecrack: or tand
oMythra: yea they wildin with the stand
knilecrack: stand*
deed02392: they are beautiful wheels though
Keyeh: LMAO
deed02392: and you don't have to get them
deed02392: lol
knilecrack: but it can have up to 1.5 TB of ram, RAM is expensive
deed02392: ecc ram no less
oMythra: you can just download RAM these days Kappa
Keyeh: does it come with 1.5 tb though? for 50k ....
deed02392: you need the extra 10k cpu for the extra ram
knilecrack: yes
Keyeh: oh ok
zigzati: @knilecrack how many players is that on my minecraft server
abrahamstr: DO u work with the cloud?
borang: f apple!!!
deed02392: @zigzati at least 3
zigzati: PogChamp
knilecrack: @zigzati :D
deed02392: PJSalt
Ch4otic: misleading title
deed02392: SSSsss
Ch4otic: or not
zigzati: @ch4otic ha U THOUGHT he was working on some math stuff
zigzati: nope CARS
Ch4otic: Yep :D
lidermaury: lately i came to conclusion that im not gonna be friend up with someone who dosent have iphone
knilecrack: rofl
samtheprogram: they have open gl, it's just not supported anymore
samtheprogram: still included in the OS
adibaby04: runs the same command even though there was an error the first time
deed02392: @lidermaury i think those people would welcome that dude
knilecrack: he probably has android
oMythra: i can't be your friend if your phine doesn't run KaiOS
deed02392: my phone is running red star os
oMythra: also phone*
smurfd0: Check where brew installs headers?
the_shining: red star?
lidermaury: George please do christmas stream where you will be talking about keyboards while programming flappy bird
borang: pls be nice to Maroon 5, best Christian band
squiggly_nibba: Listen to NF
deed02392: Christian?
OnlyB1ade: Hello George
shieeeeeeeeet: do you normally program on multiple screens?
adibaby04: what is that terminal interface? i gotta have it
adibaby04: @georgehotz
samtheprogram: i don't know about GLES though, just opengl.... i think gles is just on ios & tvos
borang: LOOKS COOL GIMME IT
lightofhel1: why do u switch from tmux to screen? @georgehotz
lllowe: search for zsh @adibaby04
knilecrack: oh-my-zsh
adibaby04: thats sexy af
samtheprogram: @adibaby04 he's running tmux almost stock, just overridden colors. he might be running zsh for the shell but has overriden the prompt to provide the exit code
adibaby04: looks like tmux
crazycatz59: Can you define noob thinking?
borang: worrying about noob thinking is noob thinking, no?
Keyeh: oh, he will go hours about it, trust me @crazycatz59
adibaby04: been programming for 3 years but never really paid attention to terminal theme lmao
oMythra: if im not mistaken it says tmux on top of the window
deed02392: Good night guys. 2 am here
oMythra: take it ez @deed02392
theselectedcoder: night deed02392
gyrojosh: nickelback lol
borang: nickleback is good too, they really put their all into their complex tunes
Keyeh: hey don't talk shit about Nickelback Kappa
the_shining: what?
brickvo: BabyRage
RSPwner_: @georgehotz what browser do you use/recommend?
the_shining: What time do you have?
oMythra: you dont want to look at this photograph, George?
ne3cross: OpenGL works fine on mac
crazycatz59: @borang yeah but how do you know? Your definition of noob thinking could be completely totally different someone else's.
crazycatz59: and plus he came up with it
adibaby04: as you can se @RSPwner_ , chromium
smurfd0: Mesalib?
Ch4otic: @RSPwner_ you can see on stream he's using chromium...
the_shining: 10.00 AM
oMythra: if im not mistaken it says chromium on top of the window Kappa
smurfd0: www.mesa3d.org
Ch4otic: why get opengl working if apple's likely just gonna remove it eventually?
Keyeh: progress PogChamp
iTzMeRafa: Pog ress
jaxnetv: use #error <msg>
Keyeh: swaglog LUL
frankytex: clamp'em where it counts!
Gtxgaming23: is this node js
Keyeh: yes
Gtxgaming23: yuck
Gtxgaming23: node is least of my favorite
Gtxgaming23: i dont understand anything from it
ranza_dk: https://glad.dav1d.de/ you can use this to generate the gles files youre missing if i remember correctly.. been a long time since i did opengl on mac
Keyeh: actually is C and python @Gtxgaming23
crazycatz59: why are we running openpilot on a mac?
Tsoding: Why not?
Keyeh: hello there @Tsoding
Ch4otic: superior OS LUL
dartrenist: the y in yaml stands for yahweh because it's godly
SlaterUSA: @georgehotz plz explain git to me :(
Tsoding: @keyeh, VoHiYo
TheRealShoks: why is it titled basic programming
crazycatz59: Are we putting openpilot on a mac so it will grow wings and fly into Tim Cook's window?
ragemaster999: where can i invest?
brbdontdie: what are your thoughts on quantum computing?
Keyeh: we are investing in apple launching their own car company LUL
Abnico: blockchain is the future of decentralization and blockchain technology
SlaterUSA: some guy just msg'd me here asking to be unbanned. i blocked him
crazycatz59: imagine not making a new account
crazycatz59: or actually
brbdontdie: I am not banned, but can I get unbanned?
SlaterUSA: some guy ending in -cat
Mariosavitch: thoughts on tesla smashing its truck with a metal ball
Keyeh: @brbdontdie playing with fire there, pal
oMythra: was it crazycatz58
SlaterUSA: no
crazycatz59: no
SlaterUSA: "myo" something
brbdontdie: the guy messaged me asking me to write unban me please LMFAO
SlaterUSA: ^
SlaterUSA: haha ok
Keyeh: banned from life Pog
Mariosavitch: he must be a tesla owner
SlaterUSA: super-banned
brbdontdie: he says that he was subbed
OnlyB1ade: Ohh triple
roystang: Hello, i have amazon prime
OnlyB1ade: OnlyB1ade subscribed with Twitch Prime.
crazycatz59: pls sub again so you can get banned for donating money
gyrojosh: pay to get banned
brbdontdie: lololol
Mariosavitch: lol
xGeoTrk: hello
knilecrack: ahahaha
oMythra: along with 0.5BTC
OnlyB1ade: HahaLean HahaLean
cccatch64: Jebaited
SlaterUSA: $4.20 or perma-ban remains in place
xGeoTrk: btw why you don't stream on Science and technology ?
crazycatz59: because science and technology is DEAD
SlaterUSA: @xGeoTrk cos he's basic, duh
3ygun: What about sending you receit for a Comma.ai package?
xGeoTrk: @crazycatz59 geohot gonna respawn it Kappa
Fantasma56: when are you cracking Japanese anime? idolAY
crazycatz59: AYAYA
Keyeh: PogChamp ?
JesseSkinner: PogChamp
crazycatz59: PogChamp
Mariosavitch: but does it blend
8430: idk what's this but poggg
Keyeh: compiled == works
Tsoding: FeelsOkayMan
zakonegrusha: @georgehotz yo geohot, how much WIndows exploit development have you done? I've seen a bit of your Linux based pwn stuff
ranza_dk: pretty sure you can fix the gles with https://glad.dav1d.de/
crazycatz59: include opengl to crash mac users cuz its deprecated ez
ranza_dk: lol is myaocat the guy that got banned? He says he'll pay you money if you unban him :D
Vesh: lil wayne slaps
R34R: what happens when you get banned? not asking for ban btw :)
brbdontdie: @ranza_dk dont get jebaited dude
oMythra: you get sent to georges blacksite
ragemaster999: just grep :)
crazycatz59: @R34R the chat box goes away and says "you are banned from this channel"
R34R: ok thanks! @crazycatz59
brbdontdie: @ranza_dk he says he can't create a new account because he "ddoesn't have email"
Keyeh: what? LUL
h4sb: weezy
ranza_dk: aww poor guy :D
da0ne_: is this how boomers code?
oMythra: make a new email?
kaney_s: he is millenial
maverick_twitch_: hello
ZemkeCWT: George is in good mood apparently.
maverick_twitch_: !info
kekisec: Hey george huge fan man <3
oMythra: thats right i forgot the blacksite doesn't have email
Mariosavitch: me :)
ragemaster999: just grep :)
MrOtotheP: grep that bad boy
btastical: if you compile with GCC you can disable warnings using -w
BlindLight2: i just used pthreads in my OS class :o
maverick_twitch_: can open pilot work in India ?
maverick_twitch_: where people dont know traffic rules
maverick_twitch_: follow*
Mariosavitch: now install good luck 2
ranza_dk: you should really check out the link ive posted :)
giacpolish: george do you code every saturday night?
oMythra: nah just when he feels like it or has something to stream
visudo20179c: sup George
brbdontdie: when did george start reading ML white papers?
Wolf_King_IV: I have no clue that the hell I am looking at here...
Wolf_King_IV: just call me an idiot and move on LUL
Mariosavitch: line 32
Mariosavitch: oh, your on a mac.. doh
guy_ross: guy_ross subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 2 months! HeyGuys
xtoledo419: GL moved? https://github.com/ziglang/zig/issues/2208
Wolf_King_IV: yup, still no fucking clue here LUL
btastical: yes making the openpilot build on mac osx
btastical: he's
Wolf_King_IV: okay
JesseSkinner: @Wolf_King_IV he runs the command to compile, sees an error, struggles to fix the error, runs the command again, and hopes to see a new error, until eventually it succeeds
Wolf_King_IV: @JesseSkinner mvp
JesseSkinner: now it compiled but the ui crashes when he runs it @Wolf_King_IV
extremelywide: favorite lang?
crazycatz59: New Error PogChamp
prvk3: what are we making today?
DyersEve15: which keyboard do you use
KrrSplat: LOL
vovnsons: @DyersEve15 monkaS
crazycatz59: still waiting for him to program that bot to automatically ban ppl who ask about the keyboard
oMythra: mentioned the K word
ranza_dk: 410
knilecrack: :D
chocolatechp: your keyboard is asmr
OnlyB1ade: HolidayPresent
oMythra: HahaHide
chocolatechp: george do you miss new jersey
LuaKT: Try 120
silverthekittenn: LUL
crazycatz59: EZ
oMythra: LUL
KrrSplat: PogChamp
knilecrack: geo is ruthless when it comes to banning
crazycatz59: ask the ppl at nvidia
ranza_dk: https://thebookofshaders.com/ :D
SkywardDev: How are you liking the new Mac 16" George?
Th3G4mingbros: what's the joke about the keyboard? Not asking for the keyboard itself but why he is banning people for it xD
SkywardDev: Was thinking of getting one myself... thing looks sweet
hardtarget4: 16" is prime. just got one too
SkywardDev: What specs @hardtarget4 ?
hardtarget4: i9 64GB 5500m
oMythra: @Th3G4mingbros playing with fire bro monkaS
SkywardDev: Hell yeah man
crazycatz59: using vim with the mau5 what
Rtc_ti5: haha
JesseSkinner: probably sick of the question @Th3G4mingbros
btastical: are you planning on doing another hackthebox sometimes?
big_coke_head: which mechanical keyboard dou use
JesseSkinner: monkaS
crazycatz59: oops
Th3G4mingbros: Understandable ig
oMythra: the peripheral that shall not be named
Th3G4mingbros: @big_coke_head You made a big mistake
PanosTrak: @georgehotz when are u gonna crack the ps4?
AlexEDM: is this George's typing ASMR stream?
big_coke_head: monkaS
TrapperMx: Kappa
Hunted9000: WutFace WutFace WutFace
crazycatz59: PogChamp
ranza_dk: because mac :D ..
esence: thank you TIM APPLE
hardtarget4: openpilot on 2020 ford explorer? PogChamp
ranza_dk: macos new security thing is ass
crazycatz59: this channel has no emotes for subbing jdotkdEhehe
JesseSkinner: does the ui run
ranza_dk: it builds
JesseSkinner: is this related to the ui or did he move to something else
PanosTrak: what is he doing?
usradm: hey
Xire2893: ui won't run due to ipc limitation on mac but built successfully
PanosTrak: @georgehotz what are u doing?
AlexEDM: this is all done in Python?
JesseSkinner: ipc limitation BibleThump
delbertooo: do you use the hhkb control key as apple command key? I always get kind of confused if I switch between my mac and ubuntu with like ctrl c and command c
JesseSkinner: oh so he's coding up a workaround to the ipc limitation in python?
crazycatz59: so you quit your job as the ceo of comma.ai to become a nomadic researcher in the Church of the New Hackers?
JesseSkinner: its badass he still has his twitch category set to basic programming
esence: What's up chat, how are y'all?
brbdontdie: feeling good, can't compain
btastical: are you planning on doing another hackthebox sometimes?
esence: @brbdontdie , having some wine too?
KNOOKEL_HEAD: hey george thanks for letting me know that i shoudn't be a n00b
Th3G4mingbros: 4am here but this is actually really interesting to watch
PanosTrak: why he doesnt like asking about keyboard?
Tarzeuss: Geohot live baby I’ve been waiting all week for this
oMythra: awww man here we go again LUL
brbdontdie: i have a final exam coming up so celebrating is for afterward
JesseSkinner: monkaS endless
esence: what class?
brbdontdie: machine learning
brbdontdie: kudos to george, this material is pretty challenging
esence: is it all theoretical?
brbdontdie: purely theoretical
brbdontdie: derivations for everything
esence: I see, what were your assignments/labs?
itsChoudhry: Does openpilot GUI use a external framework or is it a in house one?
brbdontdie: lots of materiaal, we covered bayes, k nearest neighbors, bayesiaan error, pca, lda, svm, neural net and expecation maximization
brbdontdie: and more
crazycatz59: seems pretty basic
crazycatz59: couldn't u have gotten all of that from a book?
esence: uni lectures on basics, that's ok
I_am_paranoid: why it's not in "Science & Technology" btw?
Keyeh: that's the usual stuff, not saying that it is easy by any means
purgatoires: lol yea u can learn anything from a book
JesseSkinner: you can get everything from books @crazycatz59
oMythra: yea reasonable for introductory class
brbdontdie: Yup, its my first time learning machine learning. I was more on an embedded systems track
brbdontdie: thought teh class lookoed like fun aand george made it seem interesting
esence: @brbdontdie , what degree are you pursuing, data science?
crazycatz59: but dont colleges usually only teach 1 ML/AI class and that's the material they teach?
crazycatz59: at least the ones ive looked at
brbdontdie: nope, i am doing computer engineering
JesseSkinner: he's on the old twitch category from like 2 years ago @I_am_paranoid which i think is awesome
purgatoires: and not all intro classes cover lda, svm, neural networks
brbdontdie: this class was for fun. don't need it to graduate
Th3G4mingbros: @crazycatz59 Applied Computer Science here and we got a basic introduction to ML last year with a more advanced course this year
brickvo: 4Head Just
Th3G4mingbros: but that's alll
purgatoires: my school had a stats data science major but i wasn’t interested in it at the time
knilecrack: what is passive=0 ?
oMythra: yea fuck that lol @purgatoires
esence: is data science still at the meme level?
Th3G4mingbros: for us it is :p
Keyeh: not for the guys getting paid tons
purgatoires: @omythra what u mean
JesseSkinner: my school had cs in the math faculty so i got a bachelor of math
esence: data science == conditions; change my mind
esence: we can hear your 8-core CPU
LaxantePraVaca: first time in the chat, usually watch from the youtube record
purgatoires: the term data science is so connected to “business problemsolving” that it will never not be a meme
brbdontdie: I wish i did math with a minor in cs instead of computer engineering
SonOfSatan: yo what're you doing George
oMythra: i meant that doesnt sound very interesting to me either..not n entire degree on data science anyways
LaxantePraVaca: glad to see data science is a meme here too kkkkkk
Darvein21: !uptime
Keyeh: @LaxantePraVaca fala
esence: @LaxantePraVaca , welcome
purgatoires: @omythra i mean stats is cool, i wish i did cs stats instead of mathematical econ
LaxantePraVaca: @Keyeh haha eae
esence: @brbdontdie ,why, to switch into data sci.?
anguscupcake: you can get good at math just by reading textbooks
brbdontdie: nah, I feel like some of these concepts that seem somewhat complex to me would be easier to grasp.
esence: college will not help with that, just start practicing in your spare time
oMythra: there actually a lot of good free math material out there these days
purgatoires: u can get good at math by reading textbooks, but it’s a hell of a lot easier if ur required to do it for a degree
JesseSkinner: yeah biggest benefit of school is giving you a deadline
JesseSkinner: if you can do that for yourself you're home free
esence: how is it easier? At the end of the day, you have to sit down, push through, and try to understand...
colanzio5: also it's a hell of a lot harder to find good material online when the math your'e doing becomes highly contextualized by the field you're working in.
LaxantePraVaca: @brbdontdie just get some books of math and start reading, then read their references if you don`'t get it. Getting the course plan from some courses that you're interested might help
purgatoires: bc i would not have pulled all-nighters doing math problems had i not been required to
anguscupcake: if you want to learn how to self motivate then get a book on creating habits
brbdontdie: I was thinking about going into ML white papers and just evaluating some of the current models that are being used today
anguscupcake: everything is in books mang
oMythra: yea for very high level stuff you wont find the material you need but for calc, linear algebra etc. you're fine @colanzio5
esence: I think smoking weed helps to solve all of your problems
purgatoires: white papers aren’t efficient ways to learn if ur relatively new imo
JesseSkinner: 1 esence
purgatoires: lots of textbooks out there
mutrx: what happened to doing Hack The box?
mutrx: play marbies
LaxantePraVaca: @brbdontdie papers are usually to short to learn, most of the time. Get some books of ML to learn more of the fundamentals then goes into the state-of-art through papers
JesseSkinner: not alot of viewers??
mutrx: smh how is george not playing jumpking
esence: guys, thoughts on fast.ai?
JesseSkinner: never see 200 viewers in a coding channel on twitch
mutrx: ^^^^
LaxantePraVaca: @esence looks good from what I've seen, but I didn't read alot of it thou
btastical: maybe this: https://stackoverflow.com/a/29809480/5668843 or that: https://wincent.com/wiki/@executable_path,_@load_path_and_@rpath
oMythra: its been recommened a lot by people in ML but haven't tried it myself yet @esence
knilecrack: cause noone is hot
Jelicion: George is the good looking version of Mark Zuckerberg.
btastical: oh you just opened it, nvm then
mutrx: @Jelicion minus a couple billion
purgatoires: coding vicariously thru george bc i cant code bc of an RSI flare up :(
silverthekittenn: @esence Try it. It worked for me. Few hours into it I could a food classifier b/c the content is designed for coders
brbdontdie: can anyone recommend a good book? Right now, I am going through Duda's Pattern Classification.
mutrx: Lord of the Flies @brbdontdie
purgatoires: Applied Predictive Modeling is a good overview of a lot of models
purgatoires: with exercises
esence: I've tried fast.ai, very pragmatic approach, I liked it too.
purgatoires: @brbdontdie
brbdontdie: i've put it on my sticky notes
RonDune: lots of people on github complaining about compilation issues on Mac OS X in libdbc btw
QUOTE_IF_GREEK_IS_GREASY: PogChamp george
purgatoires: Max Kuhn also came out with a. feature engineering book, i haven’t read it but it’s free online
mutrx: make a ctf for chat and first n who capture gets mod?
RonDune: see the libcanardbc docs for instance
brbdontdie: I graduate in a few days. Will probably be getting into self teaching since my company will be paying me to be an embedded software engineer
QUOTE_IF_GREEK_IS_GREASY: this guy's a pro he can do it mizkifEZ
JesseSkinner: the learning never stops @brbdontdie, you gotta run to stay in place in this industry
esence: nice, life post-school is way better. :>
brbdontdie: Maybe, if I acquire ML skills on the side, they can let me transition
QUOTE_IF_GREEK_IS_GREASY: nymnEZ
purgatoires: that’s my goal, but i’m not even in a coding job yet lmao @brbdontdie
esence: @purgatoires , apex kek, just apply for some webdev shit. so many jobs in states
Jelicion: I have no idea about programming, but it looks so easy with George's skills. His programming looks nice and artfully.
estilen: What zsh theme is that>
anguscupcake: working remotely is the best
purgatoires: i make $81k rn so i can wait ;p
silverthekittenn: why is web dev so hated?
brbdontdie: @JesseSkinner yeah man, I'm honestly looking forward to it. I can learn the things that genuinely interest me
JesseSkinner: exactly @brbdontdie its a lot of fun
purgatoires: my job is boring as hell but i have time to study after work
esence: RIP
funnlimited: LMAO
squiggly_nibba: Are there any other streamers who program?
lua_320: haha
JesseSkinner: i do @squiggly_nibba
esence: @silverthekittenn , it's because there is nothing challenging
purgatoires: @squiggly_nibba go to the science and technology section
brbdontdie: @JesseSkinner I just wish my friends were as enthusiastic as you guys
oMythra: lots check out ThePrimeagen @squiggly_nibba
funnlimited: @jesseskinner why svelte LUL
mutrx: advent of code LULW
JesseSkinner: haha @funnlimited i love it
funnlimited: you are a dedicated man
esence: wait, who's talking about Svelte?
Plurmorant: ADVENT
funnlimited: @jesseskinner @esence
squiggly_nibba: Awesome thanks guys!
JesseSkinner: i stream svelte @esence
esence: Svelte and Rich Harris is awesome
silverthekittenn: @esence I mean companies like google don't like (web) system design challenges.. I get the there're jobs that just piece together off the shelve stuff
JesseSkinner: its my favourite thing in the world right now
lebop: hi im new HeyGuys
sadpoopz: hi new
lebop: here*
purgatoires: @
lllowe: we dont care :)
mutrx: does george talk to himself alot?
sadpoopz: he talking to us
JesseSkinner: i thought he was talking to me
Jok4ndre: Hi @georgehotz , my name is Jorge (portuguese). Wasn't the streams supposed to be non comma.ai related?
esence: CLAP
sadpoopz: crashes means progress
estilen: Hey lads, what ZSH theme is geohot using?
JesseSkinner: this laptop will be driving itself around the neighbourhood in no time
mutrx: @estilen look in this dotfiles, not that any of it matters
esence: @estilen , dude, it's an ugly theme, why do you care? xdxd
QUOTE_IF_GREEK_IS_GREASY: CRASHING PogChamp
estilen: cause I like it? xdxd @esence
mutrx: yo george when we playing marbies
mutrx: multithreading in python LUL
QUOTE_IF_GREEK_IS_GREASY: mizkifCorn progress mizkifCorn progress mizkifCorn progress
esence: @estilen , google OhMyZsh, open their Git page, and scan through
QUOTE_IF_GREEK_IS_GREASY: mizkifCorn progress mizkifCorn progress mizkifCorn progress mizkifCorn progress
sadpoopz: self driving mac
QUOTE_IF_GREEK_IS_GREASY: self-driving shaq
johnATHANATOS: Hello :)
estilen: I have already, nothing seems to match @esence
Jelicion: Damn, its like fortnite, but without fun, ninja and flying twitch-thots.
esence: @estilen , I just scanned for 3s, it's called: cypher
esence: .................
esence: you're WELCOME
mutrx: what's gonna happen to comma when tesla licenses its pre-existing autopiliot technology to major car manufacturers
estilen: Mate
QUOTE_IF_GREEK_IS_GREASY: i agree:)
estilen: Maaate
kevin99gh: @georgehotz your doing great work n you are very entertaining triHYPERS <3 are you working on anything VR related triShy
estilen: I am blind
estilen: Hahaha, thanks @esence
esence: xd
esence: dummy
QUOTE_IF_GREEK_IS_GREASY: @kevin99gh you're**
estilen: nah just blind af
kevin99gh: @quote_if_greek_is_greasy triTHICC
mutrx: why python is the real question, not very performant
sadpoopz: casually pushing to master
esence: I push to master always, you gotta problem?
JesseSkinner: me too
mutrx: i thought this was going to be a minecraft stream :(
esence: @mutrx , performance is not always #1 priority
robby0313: Thoughts on aws
esence: bloated
esence: and depends on a service
Th3G4mingbros: restart terminal for symlink to work
QUOTE_IF_GREEK_IS_GREASY: OMEGALUL S X
lllowe: yes :)
esence: only Fortnite
Plurmorant: AI can't get diamonds 4Head
mutrx: minecraft will be more challenging than advent @georgehotz
erichtp: thats the wrong numba
JesseSkinner: is he PST or central
KrrSplat: AOC > Minecraft
brbdontdie: I am fairly new to veiwing on twitch stream, do the people who help already have experience working on what George is working on or are they just following along?
mutrx: minecraft will challenge @georgehotz more than advent will LUL
JesseSkinner: im just following along @brbdontdie im new here too
mutrx: @brbdontdie nobody knows what george is doing because this is stuff he's been working on for years, but we all like to thnik we all know what's going on :)
colanzio5: @mutrx he's literally just porting something to another os
prakyath_kantharaju: This is ASMR for adults
zup_zup: are you using tmux?
esence: just ask to your userbase to install VirtualBox 4Head
SGammer2142: cant you vpn in
sadpoopz: nice
mutrx: minecraft will challenge @georgehotz more than advent will LUL
esence: @georgehotz , pls cat it
zup_zup: how do you get tmux to scroll properly -- that was always my issue
IncanSilver: y'all got any of those private keys
IncanSilver: I need a private key
mutrx: only 11k commits LUL
zup_zup: what are you trying to do with commaai
IncanSilver: thanks
esence: we want your private key
btastical: now the ui fix?
mutrx: minecraft will challenge @georgehotz more than advent will LUL
brbdontdie: I want to be more useful, but I don't have a mac haha
IncanSilver: <3
esence: looks good
prakyath_kantharaju: link carla to comma ai api
MrMcaustin1: Whats up George
WhiteshooZ: wtf GeoHot is casting in the "basic programming" category
mutrx: it only ran on ubuntu before?
mutrx: pc? tf
komocode_: on a Mac Pro?
prakyath_kantharaju: install ubuntu in docker, and install openpilot in docker. And then link Carla, I think that way you wont have to build in mac os.
brbdontdie: Once I graduate, I am going to try to really follow these streams. I think I am a decent programmer, but I still have a lot to learn.
mutrx: @brbdontdie you don't learn this stuff from university
komocode_: docker has been a pain at my company. fuck docker for certain use cases
zup_zup: docker is a blessing
brbdontdie: agreed. I feel like the university setting is very limited
lllowe: @prakyath_kantharaju PogChamp
esence: 14 more mins, chill
xkrnsniperx: docker docker-compose docker swarm
xkrnsniperx: yes
brbdontdie: There is no way for the university to gauge if we "learned" a lot of these skilsl
knickerbockerr: Do we have free will George
esence: time to git reset head
sadpoopz: oh no
ne3cross: https://www.portainer.io/
JesseSkinner: all that fun for nothing?
brbdontdie: I'm excited though, George is really brilliant. Hope to learn a lot from him.
esence: that's how coding is
treyshawnsongzz: i watch full ads to support the stream
xGeoTrk: Guys which is faster ? 1)Speed of light 2)GeoHotz typing
MrMcaustin1: Geroge's typing by far
mutrx: geo isn't even that fast
mutrx: i could beat him in typeracer
brbdontdie: he looks like he can type at least 100wpm
esence: yup, give the man the money
myuchelys: done
esence: wp
kubaaa6: You think its worth to take a job with facebook working on their augmented reality?
btastical: more like 120 @brbdontdie
komocode_: thanks Apple for avoiding NVIDIA
brbdontdie: yeah, I would believe it.
WhiteshooZ: sudo that bitch
esence: there we go
xkrnsniperx: gotta run as roooooooooooooooooot
komocode_: get a Mac Pro
esence: EZ -3000 dollarinoos
myuchelys: pog 1TB
mutrx: is it terminal based UI?
esence: guys, you can order the Apple Stand.
esence: iStand
prakyath_kantharaju: @mutrx its qt
mutrx: terminal based UI @georgehotz ?
zup_zup: how do you have multiple sessions in your terminal
JelloMoto_: tmux
mutrx: @zup_zup google is your friend
WhiteshooZ: RIP_ui
komocode_: i put a terminal in your terminal so you can terminal while you're terminaling
mutrx: makes him look infinitely cooler
esence: we can
ne3cross: Tmux
sadpoopz: FeelsBadMan _ui
vloood: yes
myuchelys: sounds like that mac is cookin boi
Rlchibi: 7 mins to 9 @georgehotz
dontbeameme: Ice made u
gordopeIotudo: do you mind sharing your vimrc? @georgehotz
sadpoopz: what happens at 9
mutrx: advent of code
esence: EXITING
mutrx: @georgehotz paid a LARGE premium for that GPU LUL
MrMcaustin1: seg falt rip
WhiteshooZ: Segment Fault.. lol
knilecrack: rekt
sadpoopz: great
esence: I think you need more expensive GPU to make it run
aaronfriedland: FATALITY
ataradov: It is 7:55 in CA
WhiteshooZ: glad to see one of our times greatest programmers suffers from the same problems as I do
mutrx: yes
mutrx: who tf uses mac anyway LUL
aaronfriedland: PogChamp ARCH INSTALL STREAM
lllowe: no
MrMcaustin1: Just install arch
JesseSkinner: vm?
komocode_: give up and install counter-strike beta 5.2. someone uploaded it
CraftyGaming: Hello ther
mutrx: play Halo master collection
myuchelys: yes Linux is the best right?
myuchelys: minus the desktop part
aaronfriedland: FreeBSD or GTFO
brbdontdie: Does George play video games often?
esence: he plays Fortine quite often in this stream
gordopeIotudo: would you mind sharing your vimrc? @georgehotz
mutrx: @brbdontdie twitch's largest gaming streamer
sadpoopz: oh no
WhiteshooZ: best OS would be a very subjective answer
myuchelys: ofc
esence: he just upgraded his GPU for gaming
aaronfriedland: @brbdontdie only on Mixer where he uses the name Ninja
brbdontdie: lmfaoo
komocode_: Tim Sweeny
esence: the best os is JavaScript
brbdontdie: I usually watch the youtube videos since I always miss the stream
komocode_: what do you think about John Carmack going to research AGI
prakyath_kantharaju: First check if the container is installed, docker container ls -a, docker exec -it <container> bash to get the bash
komocode_: os TEN
smurfd0: You dont have carla in brew?
esence: npm install carla
esence: should work
julesx416: i like how the category is "Basic" Programming
aaronfriedland: ?
JesseSkinner: what does carla use unreal engine for?
aaronfriedland: this is AutoHotkey
btastical: you're going down a deep hole with building carla on mac osx it seems
esence: he's trying to launch Fortnite
esence: on mac
sadpoopz: nice
beckles: PLAY FORTNITE
aaronfriedland: PogChamp
JesseSkinner: Setting up Mono PogChamp
mutrx: i failed the HIV test :) I learned alot
esence: grats bro
gordopeIotudo: would you mind sharing your vimrc? @georgehotz
prakyath_kantharaju: @georgehotz check docker containers installed by doing docker container ls -a
knilecrack: game is hard on macos
beckles: is that just terminal in dark mode?
esence: @prakyath_kantharaju , you sent him down this rabbit-hole!
CraftyGaming: Failing in a VM is different than failing in your main OS too. Good tip for the noobs
prakyath_kantharaju: docker container ls -a
beckles: what is carla
anup_kodlekere: is that the mac's fan at full speed?
esence: @georgehotz : https://github.com/carla-simulator/carla#building-carla
knilecrack: why dont you pull the latest?
esence: "Unfortunately we don't have official instructions to build on Mac yet, please check the progress at issue #150."
komocode_: ask lex fridman if he got carla working on mac
anup_kodlekere: lol
anup_kodlekere: they have their differences
aaronfriedland: are you using an actual Mac or a regular PC with OS X installed?
anup_kodlekere: why would he do a hackintosh?
aaronfriedland: lol
delbertooo: but couldnt you x11 forward even opengl - but horribly slow
anup_kodlekere: its got a 1tb ssd? yoooooooo
delbertooo: LIBGL_ALWAYS_INDIRECT=1 or somthing
brbdontdie: lmfao
aaronfriedland: I bought an 8TB HDD two months ago and it's already dead :)
anup_kodlekere: LUL LUL LUL LUL
anup_kodlekere: I lost an external one. Had so much cool shit on it tho
aaronfriedland: @esence a sentence like that is a good way to end up on a list
anup_kodlekere: amen
Its_LilRyan: Or 2
mutrx: when r we playing minecraft
btastical: try looking into headless carla maybe? https://github.com/carla-simulator/carla/issues/1112
MrMcaustin1: Yo @esence lets not talk about CP
MrMcaustin1: f
dprophecyguy: Hi George
coProof: geo my boii
Themeow1: I was told it was easy to get banned here
Themeow1: So where is my ban
btastical: look at the headless one. I dont think carla works without providing display information
prakyath_kantharaju: go to docker bash
coProof: yay this looks fun
coProof: ME TOO GEORGE
delbertooo: god i hate dynamic linking
crazycatz59: so how is this going to let us run openpilot on a mac?
coProof: why do we have to dynamically link because mac?
MrMcaustin1: #BanLinking
hardtarget4: linking is a scam
anup_kodlekere: he does have a lot of patience though. I could never do all this i'd just break my pc
JustAnEdtior: does george have a degree?
crazycatz59: no
crazycatz59: you dont need one for what he's doing so who cares?
hardtarget4: porting is torture
fasterthanlight13: new error Pog
MrMcaustin1: Is there a headless version of carla you can use?
btastical: look at the headless one. I dont think carla works without providing display information
JeanFrag: Pog progress?
coProof: a degree in patience... isnt life just one error after the other?
crazycatz59: using an SSL series compressor on a dance kick makes no ****ing sense whatsoever
hardtarget4: rm
knilecrack: docker rm or docker rmi
coProof: F those containers
delbertooo: @georgehotz you can actually run them with --rm to remove the container after returning... like docker run --rm carla
coProof: rm -rf *
BiTvon: What hair product do you use
zeroeagle1: rm -rf /
CraftyGaming: no sudo @zeroeagle1 ?
btastical: "-ti /bin/bash"
zeroeagle1: always use sudo -r
430i: -it
zeroeagle1: first thing when you log: sudo -r
smurfd0: Tinkering=good stream :)
anup_kodlekere: @crazycatz59 wasn't that deadmau5? LUL
QuantumDota: major noob alert
btastical: https://github.com/carla-simulator/carla/issues/1112
crazycatz59: @anup_kodlekere yes
QuantumDota: good luck getting X working inside a docker container on a Mac
QuantumDota: Why aren't you using Linux, it's so much easier
crazycatz59: did you read the title?
MrMcaustin1: brb going to get some ice cream
myuchelys: =/
coProof: coProof subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 3 months! docker inside docker inside docker plz
zeroeagle1: at job we need to use some windows eocker images networking suck
crazycatz59: pog
KNOOKEL_HEAD: windows master race Kappa
KNOOKEL_HEAD: *pc randomly shuts off to download updates*
anup_kodlekere: lol
zeroeagle1: finally dominos guy came
coProof: sersly this happens a lot
crazycatz59: imagine typing ls on a directory you just created
lebop: someone ELI5 what hes trying to do thx
delbertooo: gl on this dude, i need to sleep now. waiting for the vod
anup_kodlekere: I think most problems on python can be solved by standardizing one version, or am I delusional?
coProof: gcc PepeHands
MrMcaustin1: MrMcaustin1 is gifting 6 Tier 1 Subs to georgehotz's community! They've gifted a total of 6 in the channel!
MrMcaustin1: MrMcaustin1 gifted a Tier 1 sub to vloood!
MrMcaustin1: MrMcaustin1 gifted a Tier 1 sub to leopp!
MrMcaustin1: MrMcaustin1 gifted a Tier 1 sub to MichaelA1337!
MrMcaustin1: MrMcaustin1 gifted a Tier 1 sub to dgkng0d!
MrMcaustin1: MrMcaustin1 gifted a Tier 1 sub to TheKoreanZombi!
MrMcaustin1: MrMcaustin1 gifted a Tier 1 sub to Xingjuice!
MrMcaustin1: MrMcaustin1's Gift shared rewards to 25 others in Chat!
crazycatz59: Pog
BiTvon: Relax
myuchelys: Pog
MrMcaustin1: Felt in the holiday spirit ;)
fasterthanlight13: Thanks for the HahaBall @mrmcaustin1
KrrSplat: Poggers
MrMcaustin1: Of course
MrMcaustin1: Just need george to see it now
MrMcaustin1: lol
zeroeagle1: lol gl
coProof: @MrMcaustin1 he is blind
myuchelys: @MrMcaustin1 doin the Simulation's work
anup_kodlekere: yaaay he saw
MrMcaustin1: Ill do another 4 to 6 another stream. Anything to please George
FwgKing: Can really see his happiness LUL
coProof: Mr. Simulation is happy too
big_coke_head: dodged PogChamp
btastical: half an hour to 9
ranza_dk: thats a lot of gifts
lebop: ty MrMcaustin1 !
MrMcaustin1: Of course
CraftyGaming: Didnt you already update unreal? Or what was that 9GB download you did?
lebop: why no emotes or sub icon though?
ranza_dk: wait... did you mention the keyboard?
techie163: techie163 subscribed with Twitch Prime.
MrMcaustin1: gg techie163
crazycatz59: look at all them subs today PogChamp
big_coke_head: HahaDreidel @techie163
Mabaet: !uptime
coProof: ofc F yeah lets build that unreal engine
knilecrack: why stop now?
zeroeagle1: :O
knilecrack: we believe in you
futu_rum: XD
delbertooo: @georgehotz does this ubuntu thingy have docker with docker-nvidia extension or the ability to have this?
BiTvon: Isn’t getting it running supposed to be the easy part
crazycatz59: You gotta not get a job so you can suffer by by building unreal engine
zeroeagle1: at least ur not waiting for your build on a single build CI for your team
CraftyGaming: time to write a new kernel
coProof: lets write a new kerlnel
MrMcaustin1: Time to just write the code from binary
coProof: 0101010111101
crazycatz59: twitchcoq
CraftyGaming: Well you need a different means of file relations to remove the need to build at all
big_coke_head: @zeroeagle1 oof
anirudhrautela: @georgehotz Tea time :-)
zeroeagle1: @big_coke_head the other day had to change something in every microservices took like 20 minutes...
zetleri: sup
crazycatz59: but isn't that in production
mdrake_: wait it isn't sunday yet
crazycatz59: nope
crazycatz59: still got 22 mins
Gtxgaming23: time != sunday
zetleri: its been sunday for 6h's already
MrMcaustin1: You got about 20 minutes George
coProof: Ubunut16.04
coProof: ?
Gtxgaming23: i just got here, what me making here
zetleri: LTS
coProof: @Gtxgaming23 were trying to do naughty things on a mac
Gtxgaming23: i like naughty. how naughty we talking about
zeroeagle1: stream dead?
CraftyGaming: no
MrMcaustin1: streams alive
zetleri: so slow to compile
martinstuessy: o/
MrMcaustin1: Compiling is a blessing and a curse
CraftyGaming: Remember kids, always create a gui interface using visual basic to track the killers ip address
aaronfriedland: then use LOIC :tf:
zeroeagle1: then get busted as a script kiddy
erichtp: @craftygaming using more hands at a keyboard makes typing faster
crazycatz59: @erichtp bet
aaronfriedland: but at least I get to brag to my buddies in IRC first
robby0313: When can we see more HackTheBox
Gibby5: does anyone know how git gud with vim?
esence: unbind arrow keys and just jump into it
coProof: i didnt know you released data
MrMcaustin1: Gibby5 look up vim adventures
oMythra: do the default tutorial and check out 'Learn Vim for the Last Time' by daniel miessler @Gibby5
MrMcaustin1: @georgehotz aria2
myuchelys: oh very nice, thank you @MrMcaustin1
zeroeagle1: it is now allowed to talk about comma?
MrMcaustin1: 10 minutes
CraftyGaming: definitely do vimtutor @Gibby5
zeroeagle1: proud to be part of that stream
BigBrainDota: is it allowed to talk about the keyboard?
zeroeagle1: !timeout
Vayrus_: What is he coding?
aaronfriedland: Advent of Code? Is that a programming game or something?
oMythra: a series of problems, one every day for the month @aaronfriedland
aaronfriedland: oh that's cool
oMythra: they build on each other too
Mabaet: y he doin comma ai? he say no comma related in his strims
zetleri: @georgehotz "fun"
coProof: im having fun :)
esence: no i am :)
lithiumx4900: put it in a docker? then have it listen on a port and use the port
crazycatz59: I'm supposed to be doing useful things like building art skills but instead I'm watching george raging at a compiler
electro_y0: :)
aaronfriedland: I'm just barely learning how to use Python and AutoHotkey right now. Automated one of my boring work tasks with it.
KrrSplat: 8 minutes till 9
zetleri: useful != art skills
zeroeagle1: george what happenned to the 'tomcruse" twitch channel?
prakyath_kantharaju: Damn, that looks neat. AF
esence: 5 more mins, go get some tea!
georgehotz: my.comma.ai
coProof: Apple is so big that George needs to work over break
BiTvon: Work hard play 😓 I
crazycatz59: wow, genius
MrMcaustin1: 2 minutes
raiikouu: timer monkaS
raiikouu: 25 seconds left monkaSD
khilshot: yo
jluiiizz: Are you doing AoC using python ? @georgehotz
raiikouu: When will you get your Jetskie @georgehotz
zeroeagle1: is that the AI: if A==1 :..
raiikouu: i dont understand a single word but i love it LULW
CraftyGaming: would a* fit well here?
MrMcaustin1: yeah
MrMcaustin1: but thats if we knew the map
CraftyGaming: I'm a little blind ehre but cant you build the map by moving around?
MrMcaustin1: Yes you could
mutrx: has geo been doing the previous ones or just 15?
CraftyGaming: I missed a little of the problem and only know what george is saying
MrMcaustin1: He hardly read the problem
CraftyGaming: welp, theres the map
oMythra: he did previous ones off stream @mutrx
mutrx: @oMythra ty
MrMcaustin1: Just multi thread the thing and then run a lot of them Kappa
CraftyGaming: start at a random spot every time and then launch 20 instances Kappa
zeroeagle1: if you dont know the map there are no better solution then a greedy algorithm right?
raiikouu: i agree Kappa
CraftyGaming: recursive flood fill, then A*
raiikouu: i understand everything Kappa
MrMcaustin1: If we have infinite time and memory we can solve anything in 0 time
zeroeagle1: if you explore every "node" you will a* won't be necessary
CraftyGaming: well, if you store every path taken, but that could be bad if the map is huge
CraftyGaming: and you arent guarenteed best path with flood fill
raiikouu: does he need to hurry or why isnt he looking at chat
raiikouu: nevermind
zeroeagle1: I thought the problem was to find the oxygen tank
archeadis: use pypy to speed it up
raiikouu: question answered
raiikouu: LUL
CraftyGaming: If I understand the problem, I think he nees to provide the shortest path to it
MrMcaustin1: Multithread it
ByForever: what is this? some competition?
MrMcaustin1: Yes ByForever
zeroeagle1: oh I see
Jok4ndre: what is that website?
oMythra: Advent of Code
MrMcaustin1: adventofocde.com
KrrSplat: Adventofcode.com i think
Crypod: @MrMcaustin1 code* monkaS
raiikouu: ye
MrMcaustin1: u right
raiikouu: CraftyGaming and I think hes looking for the shortest way too rn
raiikouu: he said he can backtrakc it or smth
CraftyGaming: yeah, A* uses backtracking
zeroeagle1: have you ever had to use a* at your job?
CraftyGaming: That being said, I couldnt write it myself without wikipedia
CraftyGaming: I used A* for a dumb AI in a VR game I made
MrMcaustin1: gg
raiikouu: so a* is a search algorithm yes?
unnamedtroll: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
lllowe: PogChamp
CraftyGaming: it returns shortest path
KrrSplat: PogChamp
MrMcaustin1: Yes raiikouu
raiikouu: okok
Gibby5: damn
raiikouu: im learning nice
blondephilia: Depth First LUL
CraftyGaming: or identifies it, I guess
raiikouu: learning by watching pros, jsut like league of legends
raiikouu: ezypzy Kappa
ByForever: it s impossible for me to understand hes too fast
zacho5002: zacho5002 subscribed with Twitch Prime.
CraftyGaming: a* is super cool and pretty easy to implement yourself!
MrMcaustin1: Thanks zacho5002 !!
zeroeagle1: if your goal is to learn this isn't the best place to learn practical things...
zacho5002: @MrMcaustin1 yep! putting this sub on my resume!
ByForever: do u not use ur mouse
CraftyGaming: LUL
MrMcaustin1: haha def will get you hired
zacho5002: lmao
oMythra: no need if you're good with vim and working in terminal @ByForever
erichtp: Watching this increases IQstats high enough to understand rick and morty humor
raiikouu: haHAA
Obelisk2u: what is he working on
CraftyGaming: is printing everything overhead?
raiikouu: adventofcode Obelisk2u
zeroeagle1: io slow
mutrx: @CraftyGaming pretty sure it iso
raiikouu: soemthing with ocygen
raiikouu: and a robot
raiikouu: and a map
raiikouu: thats what I know
MrMcaustin1: io is always slow
zeroeagle1: but still faster then doing a build xD
CraftyGaming: that should take that long lol
CraftyGaming: shouldn't
raiikouu: did anyone solve it alrdy?
CraftyGaming: wow, even making tmp files...verbose
oMythra: HahaShrugLeft HahaShrugMiddle HahaShrugRight
mutrx: 10 people
mutrx: have solved apready
aaronfriedland: @raiikouu https://adventofcode.com/2019/stats
raiikouu: damn
ByForever: is this mac or linux
raiikouu: mac
zeroeagle1: what is line 5 doing?
MrMcaustin1: Reading in a file and ignoring part of it
zeroeagle1: oh yeah i see
MrMcaustin1: ew n^2
CraftyGaming: does looping backwards stop the array resize error in python?
mikey9988: LUL @MrMcaustin1
MrMcaustin1: Yeah I think it does
mutrx: couldn't u just brute force the api to get a correct input LUL
MrMcaustin1: No they limit yuou mutrx
mutrx: @MrMcaustin1 makes sense
bigduddas: lol this shit seems risky af
CraftyGaming: does that mean its a 799x799 maze?
Vjasal: @georgehotz czn oxygen flow down?
MrMcaustin1: 800x800 dont forget the 0th element CraftyGaming
raiikouu: ratirlSweat my brain is melting
CraftyGaming: he did len, wouldnt that be all of them?
MrMcaustin1: oh yeah my b
CraftyGaming: georges gold star
oMythra: POG
raiikouu: so
Crypod: let it all out SwiftRage
mikey9988: PogChamp
knilecrack: what day of AOC?
SOEMBODY: PogChamp
raiikouu: what happened LUL
bigduddas: fuck yeah i was here
knilecrack: oh day 15
knilecrack: nice
mutrx: hi youtube
mutrx: LUL
treestompztv: my man
raiikouu: do they get anything after all 25 days?
SOEMBODY: monkaS
the_shining: very nice
raiikouu: is there a prizepool or just 4fun
MrMcaustin1: @raiikouu gratification
raiikouu: welp
ByForever: theres reward for this?
mutrx: serotonin
CraftyGaming: rescuing santa
raiikouu: Pog
raiikouu: Santa wuhu
Gibby5: dopamine not serotonin
Gibby5: serotonin is for pair bonding stuff
mutrx: serotonin ™ and dopamine ©
raiikouu: its just for flex ratirlFlex
mutrx: @Gibby5 Serotonin is an important chemical and neurotransmitter in the human body
mutrx: you already acquired your daily dose of serotonin™ and dopamine© @georgehotz be happy
zeroeagle1: thought 42 was always the answer
mutrx: do the impossible quiz next
raiikouu: no germans top 20 ratirlSad
CraftyGaming: #1 guy is some MIT student
ByForever: can people cheat in this by giving answers to friends?>
mutrx: i think they randomly generate the problem for each user?
jasplano: what version of javascript is this
mutrx: 3.0
3ygun: Is he tuning hyper params or something?
zeroeagle1: the newest js frontend framework
KrrSplat: You probably will have to keep building on the code everyday, small bs now will snowball later
mutrx: 372
3ygun: ooooh he's doing advent of code
KrrSplat: He just finished this day
raiikouu: he finished
7Locrian7: 7Locrian7 subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 3 months! another accidental sub, sorry no more after this
KrrSplat: 482???
mutrx: the next advent @georgehotz https://the-impossible-quiz-game.com/the-impossible
raiikouu: that was fun to watch
virtual_machine: what's he doing here?
AlexEDM: love it
raiikouu: even if i understood nothing
mutrx: that was fun
weedlord666: ya
extracheese42: ya
mikey9988: graph it PogChamp
zetleri: yes
mutrx: yes
mutrx: 99%
zeroeagle1: you still need to know what ur doing in order to write goood crap
MrMcaustin1: jcmathews we dont talk about that here
mutrx: beautiful
yaus_baus: george streaming what a nice surprise
raiikouu: damn
Knarez: spammer no spamming DansGame
the_shining: nice
mikey9988: EZ Clap
extracheese42: t hat was fun
mutrx: @mods ban jcmathews
raiikouu: 1 ^
3ygun: Failure at life LUL Kappa
leopp: Do you actually press ESC to quit INSERT mode or remap to another key?
MrMcaustin1: jcmathews last warning we dont talk about that here
mutrx: now what squadW
extremelywide: favorite lang?
yaus_baus: is this a maze
MrMcaustin1: Not a sub
raiikouu: "ask about keyboard = ban" LUL
zetleri: First rule of keyboard is not to talk about keyboard
raiikouu: ahahha
squiggly_nibba: back to Carla!
Abnico: https://paveldogreat.github.io/WebGL-Fluid-Simulation/
SOEMBODY: Why dont you talk about it
MrMcaustin1: Ha f
earthbender: monkaS
mutrx: f
mikey9988: F
yaus_baus: yeeted that mf
raiikouu: haahh f
extremelywide: @georgehotz favorite lang to use?
mutrx: what are we doing now dad
raiikouu: unlucky dude
mutrx: EXHAUSTING
raiikouu: jcmathews c u in 10 mins
aaronfriedland: @extremelywide HolyC
raiikouu: did he get place1 on any day?
raiikouu: first place*
Knarez: junk below line LUL
hmmmu: BFS
mutrx: a*?
weedlord666: djikstras
12btw_: i have see this backround befor on a other streamer TheThing
undeadman_: hi all
MrMcaustin1: a* georgehotz
mutrx: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/A*_search_algorithm
Viper4060: Sounds like a Massdrop Alt (I am not asking I am telling)
zEveery: Can u explain the challenge ? Got here right now.
CraftyGaming: wall follower is a terrible maze solver, so inefficient
CraftyGaming: Works great in person
MrMcaustin1: Facts have used wall follower irl
aaronfriedland: One day George is going to have a keyboard Peeping Tom
CraftyGaming: I'm a corn maze champion using always turn left :P
weedlord666: @georgehotz https://pragprog.com/book/jbmaze/mazes-for-programmers
MrMcaustin1: CraftyGaming right hand on the right wall always ;)
CraftyGaming: sounds like a competition is brewing
CraftyGaming: left vs right
mutrx: a*
zetleri: go left always
12btw_: Any news to the hack contest days ago`?
MrMcaustin1: Left will get you stuck in dead ends
MrMcaustin1: Or so I ahve hear
zetleri: infinite left
MrMcaustin1: Can't attest to it
aaronfriedland: there's a reason UPS drivers only turn right
CraftyGaming: well, arguably, left is the same as right
mutrx: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/A*_search_algorithm#Implementation_details
yaus_baus: http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/download?doi=10.1.1.302.4944&rep=rep1&type=pdf
CraftyGaming: theres no difference beside the sound of the word when you say it
aaronfriedland: "both sides are wrong"
AlexEDM: wikipedia always asking for money :D
CraftyGaming: I donate to wiki periodically
AlexEDM: how much, if you don't mind me asking?
CraftyGaming: enough to fund the site for a while
aaronfriedland: I donate to Chaturbate daily
AlexEDM: nice, man.
AlexEDM: lol @aaronfriedland
zeroeagle1: -always expllore un-explored then a* the closest point next to unexplored, repeat untill finish?
yaus_baus: i sent them the 3 dollars they asked for
yaus_baus: was feeling generous
CraftyGaming: oh yeah! joints!
AlexEDM: does the AD go away after that? @yaus_baus
CraftyGaming: I saw uhhh, the coding train guy do that one I think
yaus_baus: no haha
AlexEDM: LOL
yaus_baus: paintbrush algorithm sounds interesting
vloood: is he still doing openpilot on mac?
zetleri: no
bytebacon: A-star explained by Computerphile https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ySN5Wnu88nE&t
squiggly_nibba: I think he gave up
vloood: he's doing a maze solver?
CraftyGaming: I love me some computerphile
12btw_: MAC user , at the end we a bit WE SAFE , he is handicapped. from the OS
xEvilCorp: what is he solving?
mutrx: @xEvilCorp advent of code
CraftyGaming: He solved an adventofcode problem, and is now optimizing it @xEvilCorp
xEvilCorp: cool
CraftyGaming: I have my gunnar glasses on
aaronfriedland: I got a prescription for a blue tint filter from my doctor 4Head
aaronfriedland: blue light filter
aaronfriedland: it' slate
CraftyGaming: LUL I though you were getting a prescription to enhance the blue light
jcmathews: are you a happy hacker or a sad hacker?
aaronfriedland: that would incapacitate me
aaronfriedland: I have migraines like 75% of the time on average lol
CraftyGaming: 20/20 rule
bin3o: @georgehotz hire me as your intern
LovleyBarbecue: is this css?
zetleri: yes css
bin3o: Python3
CraftyGaming: scratch
LovleyBarbecue: nice i love css
aaronfriedland: my cousin's 6 year old is a scratch god
aaronfriedland: actually idk but she fucks with it a lot
zetleri: would be cooler if he was rap god
yaus_baus: lizthegray is doing advent of code too rn
xEvilCorp: what if you create a self learning ai, give senses to it, make it understand some form of structured language and logic, then make it understand all concepts and generate conclusions and then make it optimize this code for you?
zetleri: wat
aaronfriedland: appropriate username
CraftyGaming: If we create AI and control them, is it slavery?
zetleri: only if you make it pick cotton
OnlyB1ade: sick
CraftyGaming: not really within the scope of the question, but alrighty
jcmathews: !mouse
yaus_baus: tbh a cotton picking machine would take the burden of manual labor of anyone currently in that industry
yaus_baus: automation is inevitable
experimental_warrior: Hey there, what is he working on?
xEvilCorp: he's fast typing, looks like a hacker from the movies
jcmathews: yeah his key***** go fast
zetleri: buttonboard?
OnlyB1ade: clean
cogforkd: hello hello
zetleri: mechanical input device?
cogforkd: how are you doing george?
cogforkd: long time no see
cogforkd: missed you dearly!!
xEvilCorp: why does he ban viewers that ask about the typer?
CraftyGaming: shh
yaus_baus: go watch the rank about it
eshoshin: because it gets asked endlessly
Knarez: because who gives a shit what his keyboard is lol
yaus_baus: rant*
zacho5002: what chair he usin
CraftyGaming: finally, recursion!
jcmathews: !refrigerator
xEvilCorp: this thing sounds really great though
zetleri: the real question is what kinda socks he is wearing
jcmathews: change category to ASMR
eshoshin: the tea he drinks. That's the secret sauce
yaus_baus: george as a professor
not9k: what is he working on
yaus_baus: shit would be dank
cogforkd: man.. i really like your focus!!
jcmathews: hes learning visual basic
CraftyGaming: I think A* is a breadth first prioritizing paths nearer to the goal
cogforkd: i tried to fast tyoe like you... am making a LOT of mistakes while i type... any tips!!
Knarez: are you putting your junk code on github?
veomx: how is it in san diego? good city?
CraftyGaming: true
yaus_baus: the archives are incomplete
Knarez: i did mine with generators
jcmathews: is that a herman miller
bytebacon: @jcmathews indeed it is
CraftyGaming: Your solution to this problem @Knarez ?>
jcmathews: he didnt actually pee, he just went to flush so he could show off his herman miller
Knarez: ye the intcode thing, made the state stuff easy
AlexEDM: lol @jcmathews
xEvilCorp: do you watch the expanse?
cogforkd: please giev us some insights about "LIFE" and "PROGRAMMING" and "CODING" and "getting girlfriends" and "learning new things" in programming,, becomming good at coding and never turning back! please talk/rant anything
jcmathews: wanna collab @AlexEDM
yaus_baus: ^^that
Knarez: LUL
Knarez: i didnt do yesterday's yet
Knarez: dont want to write the input parser for that crap, prob do it in a bit
AlexEDM: huh? @jcmathews
coProof: okay
cogforkd: please giev us some insights about "LIFE" and "PROGRAMMING" and "CODING" and "getting girlfriends" and "learning new things" in programming,, becomming good at coding and never turning back! please talk/rant anything
yaus_baus: ^^
calmchowder: LOL
Knarez: inception o.o
yaus_baus: hell yeah
coProof: lets rant about building linux kerns
MrMcaustin1: cogforkd lets not spam the same message
h4sb: spacex
LovleyBarbecue: u smoke weed geo baby
jay_al97: hahah
cogforkd: and making money!!
colanzio5: What do you actually think about docker?
Knarez: 100 that guy is high
captionthis22: code a jarvis
coProof: follow george on insta!
CraftyGaming: I'd like to hear a good "Here's the problem with docker" rant
yaus_baus: would you live in europe
yaus_baus: i wanna move
CraftyGaming: Here we go
krnflake1: yo @georgehotz I need to know which MacOS apps you're having in your status bar on the upper right
lebop: I'd like to hear a good "Here's the problem with docker" rant
picklesareok: what a segue
knilecrack: that is the minimum for docker :)
barretois: what do you think of software engineering?
Mabaet: what u think of silicon valley s6 finale?
yaus_baus: bay area life is wack
anup_kodlekere: how's life bro
PapaDukie: do you use vanilla vim or do you have any plugins / must-have stuff in your vimrc
eaterenrgy: Opinions on using python for a long term project, whether its a good idea or not?
CraftyGaming: It's wild out there man
picklesareok: what do you not like about their values? what were their values or whatever?
the_shining: finish?
yaus_baus: i met a guy from spain today, it sounded dope
AlexEDM: you live in an apartment or house?
CraftyGaming: Python 3.8?
picklesareok: oof
chancechants: mcretHahaa
Knarez: LOL
yaus_baus: he got a rooftop suite in madrid for 1k euro/mo
AlexEDM: damn
Knarez: bro they take a 2 hour lunch break
yaus_baus: mustbenice
Knarez: siesta time
knilecrack: rofl
mikey9988: lunch break is no joke in spain KEKW
yaus_baus: bro chad neet life in spain
VANRA: @georgehotz im beginner to cp... should i just do beginner problems or read a basic book about algos
vloood: who's a death cult?
zEveery: U did any degree? Also, do u think math is really a thing to learn (like a crazy) or just have some knowledge about data structures?
lebop: why not london george
mikey9988: i hope you really mean cs @VANRA
knilecrack: come to serbia dude, I can hook you up :)
cogforkd: cogforkd subscribed at Tier 1.
anup_kodlekere: best stuff to drink?
MrMcaustin1: Thanks cogforkd
CraftyGaming: ayyyy @cogforkd
jcmathews: do you believe math was invented or discovered?
Knarez: germany?
Columbugo: yugwhaHi yugwhaHi
VANRA: @mikey9988 nahhhh cp
lebop: what do you think about LA? @georgehotz
bytebacon: come to india!
yaus_baus: thoughts on Mochizuki
mikey9988: was a joke @VANRA :)
Knarez: LUL
JeanFrag: what do you mean by death cult? idealizing suicide?
Knarez: cows are sacred asf
Columbugo: #moomoo
sk84uhlivin: @georgehotz Are you at the best point in your life
coProof: what about google coral board
bytebacon: amazing butter chicken here in India
the_shining: i come from china
mascer95: @georgehotz I’m pretty new to coding and want to do the AoC as a challenge to myself. Is there a way to see other peoples solutions?
zetleri: portugal has all drugs decriminalized
yaus_baus: inter-universal Teichmüller theory
yaus_baus: mochi's work
LovleyBarbecue: What do u think about australia
PapaDukie: is the status there based on programming abilities or $ made
lebop: Brazil
anup_kodlekere: do you like people watching your streams over doing something productive themselves?
Columbugo: hachuDisgust hachuFlag
CraftyGaming: Sometimes george's streams can be inspiring. I always practice my touch typing afterwards because im awful
cogforkd: hey george, am the same person who had asked "not to be a noob" lat time. anyway, please talking about your "how you learnt programming" and what you did to become "BETTER"
bytebacon: Which internet services do you currently subscribe to?
anup_kodlekere: it is addictive though
coProof: the optimization function is twitch
JeanFrag: your stream makes me continue thinking about coding, it would be great if you did it more often @georgehotz
jay_al97: I actually sometimes watch your stream while working
MrMcaustin1: You become programming
yaus_baus: programming learns you?
WOLVESpls: 4Head
the_shining: What time is it there?
veomx: learning by doing
CraftyGaming: c bad example lol
TalonFire: literally zero people know C
blondephilia: Then maybe you know it. haha
jcmathews: favorite free key***** p*** sites?
coProof: then just die
picklesareok: you marinate yourself in code
coProof: Kappa
mutrx: is @georgehotz smoking again
MrMcaustin1: Its all about the journey
SaltMyDalt_: why do you like open source
coProof: just type "rm -rf /" you become programmer
veomx: you maybe on tomorrow`?
Knarez: whats your bedtime big guy
CraftyGaming: Time for bed, have a good night folks
Columbugo: the journey PogChamp
mutrx: what Ke- wait nvm...
MrMcaustin1: Night CraftyGaming
CraftyGaming: <3
lebop: what do you think about the Lua language? @georgehotz
anup_kodlekere: how long do you sleep?
mutrx: can i be a mod
zetleri: how wide is your bed
mutrx: :)
PapaDukie: do you like physics
AlexEDM: lol
mutrx: its a single bed
knilecrack: HOW WIDE IS YOUR BED AHAHAHAHAHA
yaus_baus: apartment tour
coProof: what is the depth of your bed
mikey9988: LUL
Mabaet: what does snails even do
supremezy: what do you think about ai in stock market and forex and such
picklesareok: LUL
canyoufeelitnowmr_krabs: what size is your bed? king?
Knarez: is that your bed in the background LUL
AlexEDM: what's the surface area of your bed?
hildl0rdi: hildl0rdi subscribed with Twitch Prime.
canyoufeelitnowmr_krabs: what food do you eat at 3am
jcmathews: does your !refrigerator have a crushed ice function
forkdb: Did you please answer my question?
MrMcaustin1: Thanks hildl0rdi
yaus_baus: snails are food for french people
Knarez: what's the optimal breakfast
vtcN_: i've always wondered how many miles of toilet paper the average human being uses in a lifetime
lebop: thoughts on the Lua language
anup_kodlekere: hows the cloud
veomx: why we have two hours time difference?
mutrx: do you cut ur bread diagonally or in half?
AlexEDM: hahaha
yaus_baus: holt
yaus_baus: holy
vloood: you should switch to wipes bruh
yaus_baus: get this man a bidet
jcmathews: does your toilet water flush clockwise or counter clockwise?
picklesareok: front to back, or back to front?
Columbugo: do fish drink water? yugwhaG
mutrx: do you cut ur bread diagonally or in half??
coProof: we need to cut back :)
vtcN_: lol
knilecrack: clockwise bro north hemisphere
LovleyBarbecue: I shit 4 times a day
AlexEDM: that's nothing - I could easily top that!
TheRockingM: Bidets for everyone
colanzio5: Literally spent an hour yesterday googling snails after eating an edible fml SabaPing
Knarez: live to be 100 goddamn
AlexEDM: also, you didn't account for all the diarrhea I have
thezilion: @georgehotz honestly, the question frequently: linux or windows?
yaus_baus: we stay shitting for 20 miles cuz
coProof: once
lebop: @georgehotz answer pls
picklesareok: isnt it a bit weird that we shit and piss into literal gallons of fresh water
mutrx: in the toilet duh
cogforkd: This is my question@georgehotz hey george, am the same person who had asked "not to be a noob" lat time. anyway, please talking about your "how you learnt programming" and what you did to become "BETTER" bytebacon:
vtcN_: run outta water LMAO
coProof: yeah we will though it will turn to h39
picklesareok: we're not gonna run out of salt watter
coProof: h3o
veomx: ice cubes
yaus_baus: it flows off the edge
Conadora: hotz do you bug bounty?
supremezy: what about sewage
coProof: donald trump argument NotLikeThis
picklesareok: stars can do that
mutrx: what is the last thing you bought on amazon
anup_kodlekere: massenergyohmy
JeanFrag: well not more than what it cost, at least right now
WOLVESpls: LUL
euranymous: MindBlow
vloood: free macdonalds apple pie on uber eats
TheRockingM: we should go with thorium for now
mutrx: wind and solar is better than nuclear
Columbugo: !uptime
anup_kodlekere: nah nuclears better
coProof: so are we okay in the future mr geohot?
JustAnEdtior: hi george
forkdb: Please answer my question..
vloood: yeah 2
yaus_baus: oh shit
forkdb: Am dying to hear from you
Gorums_1: are we in a simulation?
the_shining: Do you like noodles
jc_alvaradov: jc_alvaradov subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 3 months! love you geo
veomx: pickle rick!!
canyoufeelitnowmr_krabs: @Gorums_1 yeah the next patch is taking too long to ship
mutrx: is orange man bad?
euranymous: what do you think about Elon Musk? I think he's over rated and he is just doing everything for business
yaus_baus: is mars a scam
mf_slim: if you got your nipples pierced would you get bars or rings?
knilecrack: you should have your podcast high-talk show
coProof: the moon was a scam :)
lebop: thoughts on Lua @georgehotz
zetleri: yes
yaus_baus: podcast
knilecrack: no politics
yaus_baus: id pay
bytebacon: watch the octohedron series: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GctjEwP_gkY&list=PL48gf6Pmx2jn9BglnSU6_q3P7ZBSubK_V
JeanFrag: not only politics would be better
knilecrack: you said no politics in the channel
mutrx: joe rogan
AlexEDM: TED Talk instead
MrMcaustin1: Joe ROgan
jcmathews: when did nelson mandela die
WOLVESpls: LUL
zetleri: yeah you should go JRE
mutrx: joe ROGAN
knilecrack: rofl
coProof: must watch a lot to perfect those impressions
anup_kodlekere: do some ASMR whispering
forkdb: Your thoughts on Julia?? Or you like python??
vloood: you don't have enough vocal fry
Columbugo: ok boomer LUL
yaus_baus: npr is audio hypnotism for bay area commuting
euranymous: okay boomer
mutrx: are traps gay?
coProof: KKonaW
WOLVESpls: ASMR Kreygasm
myuchelys: Pelosi looks like she constantly having a seizure
Knarez: bedtime storys feelscomfyman
jcmathews: this is almost as calming as your beating your key*****
blondephilia: don't think he can answer about Elon. He offered him a job.
bytebacon: panda support for cybertruck!
Knarez: bernie is 78 :(
euranymous: Elon is just another business man. change my mind!
mutrx: why is this a wholesome stream all of a sudden
AlexEDM: the screens within a screen are hypnotizing
picklesareok: big if true
anup_kodlekere: what about Apple?
MrMcaustin1: Andrew Yang
ethancruize: sorry im not a subscriber im poor, but when is hacking/ctf agiain ?
anup_kodlekere: YangGang
mutrx: did you see his anime intro?
big_coke_head: how r u gonna spend ur yang bucks
jay_al97: space x is cool but Im not too hopeful of the project
zetleri: hatGAme
SimStig: spacex is rocking at the moment
veomx: elon is from the future... he scared me talking about AI :D
mutrx: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=K1jUJ-2MsdA
canyoufeelitnowmr_krabs: we need ubi so i can order more food to my house
Knarez: have you ever worn the maga hat in public? LUL
mutrx: unwarranted
AlexEDM: you need Nightbot :D
MrMcaustin1: AlexEDM nah he got me
euranymous: @georgehotz what kind of narcotic are you tripping on?
anup_kodlekere: just pull the cables
Knarez: you'd get SHIT on lmao
SimStig: AI is overblown... its still coded by humans
bytebacon: L-Theanine
mutrx: im calling the police rn
MrMcaustin1: Checks his watch to see if hes on drugs
AlexEDM: lol
colanzio5: I mean, if you think about Elon as a character like Geohot is a character the AI thing makes more sense
12btw_: How mutch the GOV pay you?
banned4mysins: hey george, do u have an advice about starting machine learning? i have math background but dont want to waste time o uni
yaus_baus: was gonna comment on watch
euranymous: oops this is a Christian channel
MrMcaustin1: hmmm
MrMcaustin1: sus
yaus_baus: oh its 1025
Knarez: will you be streaming adventofcode again tmrw?
knilecrack: damn
veomx: amen
zetleri: hotz is siliconvalley lsd microdoser
mutrx: make a christian minecraft server
mutrx: how much wam
anup_kodlekere: hallelujah
myuchelys: lmao
MrMcaustin1: Medium is wack
picklesareok: microdosing is for pansies
Knarez: cringe
mutrx: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wsO-Td0hqXo
knilecrack: medum posts are sometimes retarded as fuck
vtcN_: @picklesareok real men overdose
bytebacon: Stream on structure from motion and camera pose estimation
mutrx: watch the youtube its worth it
coProof: sudo apt-get more-ram
euranymous: The power of Christ compels you. Elon is just another businessman
12btw_: !sr PWv7FVA7MIw
TalonFire: what size SSD you got?
jcmathews: shampoo?
Senpai_Teach: you can spoof it ?
mikey9988: EZ free ram
coProof: i dont believe it
mutrx: what toilet paper do u got
anup_kodlekere: 1TB
TalonFire: PogChamp
knilecrack: he uses news paper
yaus_baus: is hair conditioner a scam
anup_kodlekere: LUL LUL
euranymous: do you like Leopold keyboards?
subconix: hair conditioner is a scam. Buy a 2 in 1
TalonFire: LUL
MrMcaustin1: DEDOTADED WAMMMM
WOLVESpls: this guy is a legend
knilecrack: ahahahahahaha
Senpai_Teach: HahaDoge HahaBall HahaDoge HahaBall HahaDoge HahaBall HahaDoge HahaBall HahaDoge HahaBall HahaDoge HahaBall HahaDoge HahaBall HahaDoge HahaBall
mutrx: the awkward moments are gold
forkdb: Julia or python?
knilecrack: ahahahaha
vtcN_: very tehcnical
myuchelys: @georgehotz any comments on future of tech? programmng? cloud? system administration? devops? love to hear insight from someone with your knowledge
veomx: maybe she should take out the nugget shile speaking
veomx: while
coProof: yes ofc how much ram do i need for 100 player server
anup_kodlekere: highly technical
vloood: what is that speech impediment called? seems common for techies
yaus_baus: where to do disorganized programming
coProof: actually a good question and no one could answer
mutrx: the bronx speech impediment
picklesareok: agile development
anup_kodlekere: whens tomcr00se the rapper in you is coming back?
AlexEDM: what should people learn to help themselves be better employees within their Fortune 500 company?
mutrx: how do i find a girlfriend
mutrx: getting to the real questions
Knarez: george was homeschooled confirmed
knilecrack: google it
AlexEDM: lol
J3rwin: lol
yaus_baus: roasted
AlexEDM: damnit man
bacon_sizzle69: oh snap
mutrx: post link in chat
SimStig: lol
georgehotz: https://imgur.com/r/wowthanksimcured/FwSA5
AlexEDM: was expecting a serial answer
WOLVESpls: Lul
veomx: im already in slavery
coProof: F word get out
knilecrack: one more podcast roast with geo hot
mutrx: it was jordan peterson
anup_kodlekere: piperCoin
AlexEDM: i'll read it later, thank you kind sir
bytebacon: Review this paper: Pseudo LiDAR for depth esttimation https://arxiv.org/pdf/1906.06310.pdf
blondephilia: can i get the link again
mikey9988: LUL
veomx: since im married lord of the rings makes really sense
picklesareok: LUL
vloood: SF sucks for finding a wife
yaus_baus: oh yeah
yaus_baus: why u no go to neurIPS
veomx: i still look for the mount doom
vloood: lot of goblins
SimStig: Been trying open pilot on n
banned4mysins: george,is it realistic to have a career in machine learning while being self taught ?
SimStig: snowy roads
Knarez: think of it as gaining xp by fighting monsters
12btw_: !sr qY0c_DByPb8
anup_kodlekere: rap for us
zetleri: pseudo-lidar
bin3o: @georgehotz lemme be your intern
mutrx: are you an apple fanboy?
NefariousPulsar: What do you know about ndn (just heard of it)
euranymous: apple is trash
12btw_: Hoppy
12btw_: or with BB
J3rwin: oh boy
mutrx: "hobby"
yaus_baus: fuck yeah singing stream
coProof: yeah you got this i teach voice lessons in the mission
knilecrack: where is our internet
anup_kodlekere: how do you find songs like these
myuchelys: Pog
mutrx: this is defs how u end up like snowden
AlexEDM: how could he not? 192 views in 3 years. shit's blowing up
coProof: foreign rap skill 100
yaus_baus: how do you explain this to other people
lemonboxed: french Eminem
chancechants: PATH OF SNOWDEN
veomx: boris
euranymous: tomcr00se will return soon
AlexEDM: you slav you lose
buhrmi4tw: boris johnson
anup_kodlekere: fluffy rabbits and teddybears
Cs_nothing: !uptime
veomx: bro if you would try in german i would celebrate :D or spanish
mrigor: slishish, can you hear?
Cs_nothing: How long has he been on for guys?
yaus_baus: hes right
mrigor: ^
mutrx: listen
chancechants: hot chick
yaus_baus: thats what it means
knilecrack: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5ESynU09urg
yaus_baus: "do you hear?"
knilecrack: some real russian
yaus_baus: yea
mrigor: ya
MrMcaustin1: George about to make this guy's video blow up
mutrx: the translation is literally to the left
NefariousPulsar: NLSR my bad
mutrx: logan paul vs KSI who should have won
AlexEDM: you should try Dark Mode on YT. it's amazing
mutrx: @AlexEDM you have to sign in
mrigor: @georgehotz link it
AlexEDM: yeah
veomx: :D oh yeah
georgehotz: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ldK9qvRBkMI
georgehotz: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=v4rvTMBCJD0
yaus_baus: Free Maksim Yakubets??
coProof: do you sprekenzy russian?
veomx: drink a bottle vodka and go
jay_al97: is that what you use YT for?
vloood: lol wtf
knilecrack: ja ne ponimaie po ruski
yaus_baus: yea
mutrx: watch unusual videos
ataradov: Wow, this is actually very good
yaus_baus: yeah
AlexEDM: da
mrigor: the slang is hard to get even for russian speakers, don't feel bad :)
cogforkd: looks like george does not like me, and he does not like to answer my questions... :( :( george ... please julia vs python? why are you not making use of julia?
veomx: works for spanish with tequilla
JaeGeeTee: DOS VAYDOHNYAH
funwayz: never thought that george would watch russian battle rap
vtcN_: russia speaks you
coProof: LULW
cogforkd: :)
cogforkd: am happy
AlexEDM: Julia Roberts
aaronfriedland: macroeconomists apparently
bytebacon: Insane freestyle rap: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NdTalMWrQ7c
cogforkd: george like me!!
cogforkd: hehe
yaus_baus: get the vodka
yaus_baus: authentic russia cosplay
mutrx: i've seen that, it's not that good
mrigor: yeah that guys is incredible
12btw_: Fake room
veomx: :D yeahhh
veomx: i dont want make you drink george
knilecrack: nooooooooooo
veomx: :D
chancechants: hotzception
yaus_baus: cmonbruh
codevisionary: what is this inception?
mikey9988: WutFace wtf
Kemisdan: White Claw
aaronfriedland: KKona
zetleri: LOL bud light
yaus_baus: slavs in chat disappointed
chelsiquixote: good evening George!
knilecrack: vodka lemon soda water
Abnico: aderall vs coffee
12btw_: This guy need 45min to get food rdy to eat
mutrx: this is normie shit
mutrx: did you see the American Psycho Programmer
aaronfriedland: George you should fuck around with Quantconnect sometime and start a hedge fund
AlexEDM: hahaha
MrMcaustin1: George do you know bo burnham
AlexEDM: George's real AF
picklesareok: this inforgraphic is really good
12btw_: Explain ASN.1
mutrx: step 2 is impossible
chelsiquixote: hows the new macbook pro 16"
mutrx: have you seen "If American Psycho were about Programmers"
bytebacon: Do nootropics really work?
thuganalyst: No George you should start a quant fund
mutrx: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uHt01D6rOLI
mrigor: @georgehotz hows sd compared to sf
AlexEDM: thank YOU
aaronfriedland: you could have the first profitable quant fund
NefariousPulsar: What do you know about NLSR
veomx: thx bro
AlexEDM: haha
knilecrack: pleaes bro
codevisionary: what happened to switching to Arch?
mutrx: so many calories in beer
MrMcaustin1: BUY A JET SKIII
funwayz: LUL
chelsiquixote: HAHAHA
knilecrack: don't talk BS
yaus_baus: boomer
zEveery: @georgehotz u should really try: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=e_xGeZDk3Sw
veomx: Hofbäuhaus Bavaria
AlexEDM: bottled water tbh
chancechants: KappaHD
JaeGeeTee: George, you should just become a cosplayer.... show your boobs so you can be rich.
12btw_: My beer has more beer in it
Kemisdan: White Claw
mutrx: too many calories
mutrx: lmao
anup_kodlekere: whens the next stream
iPOdk: light lol
mutrx: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uHt01D6rOLI
aaronfriedland: get one of those 10% natty seltzers
biGtheriG: natty daddy > bud light
chelsiquixote: whats your sleep schedule like?
vtcN_: show bobs and vagene
Abnico: nice saint laurent
zEveery: @georgehotz https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=e_xGeZDk3Sw Put at 3:10
12btw_: BOOB CGI effect PogChamp
AlexEDM: haha
mutrx: Clap Clap
tris790: did you just start stream ?
thezilion: @georgehotz react your rap music Kappa watch?v=9iUvuaChDEg
JaeGeeTee: natty light is bread flavored LaCroix
12btw_: Clap Clap
yaus_baus: what happened to the discord and shit
MrMcaustin1: George Hotz Meme review
zEveery: u gonna like it haha
aaronfriedland: real heads drink coffee soylent with gin
NefariousPulsar: Try Tecate
mutrx: react stream
chancechants: mcretHahaa FBCatch
mutrx: ok make a slack then LUL
12btw_: We doing that not here
mutrx: 4chan thread
codevisionary: agreed.
aaronfriedland: how about Microsoft Teams
myuchelys: booby streamer prob more cashflow than IG influencer @georgehotz
JaeGeeTee: lol @ microsoft teams
veomx: instagram
vtcN_: iMessage group chat
MrMcaustin1: Make us an IRC channel
12btw_: Show more Skinn is late
AlexEDM: "when"
AlexEDM: you mean "if"
bytebacon: domain dead?
veomx: :D
aaronfriedland: lol
yaus_baus: shill
chancechants: SLIDE IN HER DMs
AlexEDM: i already follow you
AlexEDM: :)
IbraMiharbi: gonna drop out of uni v can i come work at commai
knilecrack: bro your blond chick will check the stream and dump yo ass
AlexEDM: damn that's true
mutrx: that wasn't on the infographic...
Kemisdan: fax
JeanFrag: you also need that verified mark there
aaronfriedland: are you trying to farm Instagram followers so you can start a MLM scheme
WOLVESpls: LUL
biGtheriG: LUL
mutrx: don't u already have a girlfriend or is this some parallelism
knilecrack: no checkmark no chicks
anup_kodlekere: sue instagram
zEveery: I really like "sued by Sony" quote.
12btw_: You OUT with bud light
aaronfriedland: just create a shit ton of fake George Hotz instagram profiles and send Instagram a complaint about them
mutrx: do a tindr stream
aaronfriedland: ez checkmark
myuchelys: just hack instagram and put your own checkmark bro
myuchelys: you're fuckin george hotz
JeanFrag: wait isnt it more efficient to just bot followers? @georgehotz
aaronfriedland: LMFAO
WOLVESpls: LUL
thezilion: @georgehotz this is a gold https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9iUvuaChDEg Keepo
veomx: like this geocold :D
knilecrack: what happened with that Elon musk lawsuite ?
anup_kodlekere: you should actually be getting a checkmark at 17k
yaus_baus: shill ig followers with trash youtube programming tutorials
mutrx: who do u follow
AlexEDM: that profile pic is gold
chelsiquixote: did anyone else buy TSLA after the cybertruck reveal pull back?
12btw_: Is hard to move on from the modem days.
JaeGeeTee: 17.8k is very respectable
Abnico: i have check mark with 2k lmao
aaronfriedland: deepfake yourself onto a male model
blondephilia: TSLA 10k in 5 years or less
mutrx: what other trades u doing
squiggly_nibba: https://www.instagram.com/hotz8820/
Abnico: employes used to have a few to give out
WOLVESpls: ^ money flips Pog
mutrx: wow no forex LUL
aaronfriedland: OTC LUL
chelsiquixote: you should buy some NTDOY
vtcN_: SPY
mutrx: airbus is dead
12btw_: omg stil in the stock market
anup_kodlekere: you bought a plane company?
anup_kodlekere: woow
aaronfriedland: start trading TVIX on trump tweets
myuchelys: lmfao
JeanFrag: @georgehotz why not just get etf? ._.
anup_kodlekere: LUL LUL
Abnico: buy augur coin, best investment
mutrx: HAHAH
JaeGeeTee: follow https://www.instagram.com/arbitrage.andy/?hl=en for trading meme's
Crypod: hi me!
myuchelys: "I got in after the second Boeing crash"
thezilion: PYPL
chelsiquixote: even though MSFT really high right now. i kinda want to buy some
aaronfriedland: you can make a shit ton of money on PredictIt spreads
12btw_: buy cheeep
mutrx: buy high sell low
squiggly_nibba: https://www.instagram.com/hotz8820/ hack my friend Facebook
aaronfriedland: yeah but I'm poor so it's a shit ton
vtcN_: r/wallstreetbets
knilecrack: sell cheaper
mutrx: did you see the Guh meme on r/wallstreetbets
anup_kodlekere: hotzofwallstreet
MrMcaustin1: https://reddit.com/r/wallstreetbets is great
aaronfriedland: I made more money on the UK Election market than I did at my job lmao
12btw_: I will never bet on dead bodys
vtcN_: GUH
yaus_baus: GUH
aaronfriedland: yeah boris
yaus_baus: what a legend
mutrx: https://youtu.be/A-tNkuYV4_Q?t=38
mutrx: please watch
JaeGeeTee: Decent trading meme's but not as good as arbitrage andy: https://www.instagram.com/thetradingmemes/?hl=en
thezilion: check paypal
mutrx: this kid exploited infinite leverage
mutrx: and got rekt
knilecrack: @yaus_baus where are you from brah?
NefariousPulsar: Favorite movie
aaronfriedland: people were pumping corbyn and there was a 5 cent spread on his contracts
mutrx: https://youtu.be/A-tNkuYV4_Q?t=38 kid used a glitch on robinhood and got infinite leverage
chelsiquixote: anyone want to buy my music streaming royalties?
bryanhacks: PYPL
JeanFrag: that is great vid
aaronfriedland: lmao
yaus_baus: legend vid
aaronfriedland: the robinhood guy
yaus_baus: hall of fame
aaronfriedland: hahaha
JaeGeeTee: omg, i love this vid.... i
Kemisdan: LUL
vtcN_: hahahaha
veomx: wtf
mutrx: HAhahaha
aaronfriedland: did he get sued?
mutrx: LUL
JaeGeeTee: no, but robinhood got a big time slap on the wrist.
yaus_baus: 25x
aaronfriedland: fucking options too
mutrx: GUH
thezilion: honestly, this is so better watch?v=9iUvuaChDEg
yaus_baus: watch the youtube video
blondephilia: :(
vtcN_: robinhood let him leverage 25x lmao
mikey9988: F
chelsiquixote: this is devastating
yaus_baus: r/wsb yoloer does wild shit
funwayz: yolo
mutrx: wallstreetbets
yaus_baus: wallstreetbets
aaronfriedland: you can't even get 3x leverage if you're a broke kid let alone 25x
MrMcaustin1: wab = wallstreetbets
12btw_: AAPL going down
mutrx: COngrats on ur new debt LUL
JaeGeeTee: how is so calm?
JaeGeeTee: HOW IS HE SO CALM!?
aaronfriedland: he lost it all LMFAO
vtcN_: he got his shit pushed in
thezilion: @georgehotz react your old movies on youtube
mutrx: he did it once before
12btw_: haha
JaeGeeTee: my palms are sweating!
blondephilia: hahaha
mutrx: at least BitMEX doesn't margin call
aaronfriedland: @georgehotz better explanation https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-11-05/robinhood-has-a-glitch-that-gives-traders-infinite-leverage
chelsiquixote: thats devastating
JeanFrag: if you watch his vid upload he is at it again after saying he was stopping LUL
mutrx: i don't think bitcoin will ever take off as a currency
chelsiquixote: GEORGE where can i get 100% cotton sweat pants?
OnlyB1ade: hello
OnlyB1ade: there
chancechants: mcretY
vtcN_: the week this happened was so much fun to watch on wsb lmao
yaus_baus: whenever r
MrMcaustin1: https://reddit.com/r/wallstreetbets is great
chancechants: thats an oopsie
yaus_baus: r/wsb reaches front page, you know the story is good
Columbugo: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SvjwXhCNZcU watch this its entertaining
aaronfriedland: WSB is up there with IllegalLifeProTips IMO
mutrx: Legal**
yaus_baus: investment stream??
JaeGeeTee: <3 wallstreetbets
mutrx: sort by top
aaronfriedland: @georgehotz Understanding eWhoring - IEEE https://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/8806721
cogforkd: @georgehotz how many stackoverflow points do you have? is it even important to have high points for a working professional?
vtcN_: its like 4chan found a bloomberg terminal LUL
mutrx: sort by top again
aaronfriedland: gotta sort by top lots of shitposters
mikey9988: monkaS
httpsdubdubdotcomm: try obs
chelsiquixote: peace out all
aaronfriedland: LUL
12btw_: I mute you must watch this clip https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9rcIJIWqYmo
vtcN_: that's literally the subs tag line lmao
iPOdk: wtf is this
mutrx: https://www.reddit.com/r/IllegalLifeProTips/comments/e8lnbw/ilpt_if_you_sell_drugs_use_uber_instead_of/
JaeGeeTee: lmao... Hi, I'm George... I'LL HACK AN IPHONE, A PS3, CARS, BUTTTTTT I WONT SIGN INTO NETFLIX..... TOO MUCH WORK....?????
SuX_X1: !uptime
cogforkd: @georgehotz how many stackoverflow points do you have? is it even important to have high points for a working professional?
vloood: it's not really the poor, it's like middle class techies, but yeah
JaeGeeTee: <3
vtcN_: robinhood posted on wsb and they banned their account lmao
SuX_X1: :(
cogforkd: ok ok./.. got it
picklesareok: the people who love robinhood are the same people who are gonna get rich selling yeezys on stockx
aaronfriedland: the posters on that sub are the scum of the earth I love it
aaronfriedland: bunch of /r/shoplifting refugees
aaronfriedland: yep
yaus_baus: long time ago
Kemisdan: F
JaeGeeTee: what was r/shoplifting?
thezilion: RIP deepdotweb
lek0cs: F
MrMcaustin1: decentralized internet who
Crypod: Pied Piper? LUL
iPOdk: is this guy drunk?
yaus_baus: pacman -Syu freenet
knilecrack: you will able to buy drugs everywhere
lek0cs: i like the internet oof 2008 ish
funwayz: sellout
knilecrack: How much % has bud?
anirudhrautela: Nothing exists for free
cogforkd: i have 88 points on stackoverflow.. am better than you... NOT :)
lek0cs: free and trash n fun
thezilion: freenet is cool
lek0cs: you were good internet 2007
yaus_baus: decentralized bro
aaronfriedland: bring back arpanet
yaus_baus: dude i drank coors and lost my voice
thezilion: p2p
mutrx: blockchain internet
onu4r: dude pipernet is the future
yaus_baus: that beer is poison
Columbugo: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SvjwXhCNZcU watch this pls
lek0cs: ARPANET IS ONLINE
aaronfriedland: EFF 4Head
JaeGeeTee: AARON JONES!!!! SAVE US!
mutrx: @Columbugo its not even that good
mixtape089: Everyone after watching Silicon Valley
aaronfriedland: Richard Stallman is gonna save us all
onu4r: alcohol is a real life dropout to prevent overfitting
OnlyB1ade: Oxxxymiro
JaeGeeTee: lol @ stallman
vloood: it'd be funny if you went crazy and became like weev or mcaffee
OnlyB1ade: tf
knilecrack: no you are crazier
mutrx: true
yaus_baus: too rational
aaronfriedland: gotta kill someone first
lek0cs: who's weev? @vloood
mutrx: no balls
JaeGeeTee: didn't mcaffee open a flight school for some home made flying machines???
yaus_baus: not enough holyC
iPOdk: Nobody said you were crazy... you just waste your time laughing at nonsense on the internet :)
JaeGeeTee: what a looney
PoonGalore: penis
OnlyB1ade: what do you think hinton
aaronfriedland: @lek0cs a jewish nazi who can code
iPOdk: I waste my time, looking at you
JaeGeeTee: ipo dick... lmao...
iPOdk: Basically same thing
mikey9988: wtf too far @georgehotz
cogforkd: you are talented ... you shgould teach coding
iPOdk: Yes, I do have one JeeGeeTee
lek0cs: @aaronfriedland a judas priest huh
mutrx: girls coding camp
jc_alvaradov: best content on the internet
mutrx: u got any good memes?
JeanFrag: why dont you have a cat or dog? doesnt it provide a great emotional benefit with low cost in most cases?
knilecrack: ipo says something about wasting time, bro is watching another dude watching stupid stuff on internet
donald3767: Has anybody tried to acquire comma?
aaronfriedland: goerge has #blackgirlmagic
yaus_baus: #500daysofcode
Columbugo: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SvjwXhCNZcU stupid content
lek0cs: girls coding school by geohotz
hailh2o: why do u follow fortnite streamers
JaeGeeTee: i thought this was a relationship advise stream.... am i lost?
mutrx: let us inside trade comma
vtcN_: the key to life: just live forever
OnlyB1ade: can lose
OnlyB1ade: then
yaus_baus: george ayahuasca is decriminalized in oakland
mutrx: pump and dump KommaKoin
yaus_baus: stream it
aaronfriedland: mushrooms decriminalized in denver
cogforkd: your thoughs on "vitalik buterin"
mutrx: do u enjoy streaming
blondephilia: @yaus_baus poggers
JaeGeeTee: lets trade pokemon cards again.
blondephilia: LSD
vtcN_: DMT
blondephilia: DMT
lek0cs: its the Joe Rogan drug
yaus_baus: dmt soup bro
OnlyB1ade: thought on Future of computation
cogforkd: ?your thoughs on "vitalik buterin"
JaeGeeTee: i thought DMT was scheduled.
yaus_baus: https://www.insider.com/oakland-california-vote-to-decriminalize-psychedelic-drugs-2019-6
JeanFrag: do you really think that if you are "uploaded" to virtual that would still be you? @georgehotz
yaus_baus: bro not lying
thezilion: drugs is cool
aaronfriedland: LUL
knilecrack: cool while you have money
iPOdk: I stirred in some pot, wasn't ment to make you all go full defensive mode guys; as stated i'm no better - it's just a tiny bit sad.
donald3767: Moses was on DMT in the Bible
mutrx: TikTok duh
aaronfriedland: Juuling
cogforkd: coding is COOL
JaeGeeTee: trading memes are cool.
lek0cs: papa johns is cool recently
OnlyB1ade: literally
yaus_baus: go make lsd underground in the netherlands
iPOdk: I agree with hotz, goverment bs
veomx: AI girlfriends
zacho5002: white claw
picklesareok: going outside is cool
mutrx: tiktok
cogforkd: TEACHING CODING BY IS COLLER
bytebacon: You should check with Joe Rogan
lek0cs: the day of pizza reckoning is coming
mutrx: did u watch Joker movie?
Columbugo: Tiktok is very cool Kappa
mikey9988: cmonBruh popa ?
OnlyB1ade: just said it
mixtape089: AI is cool
aaronfriedland: @georgehotz why aren't you on twitchstocks.com
httpsdubdubdotcomm: new cool.....learn to mumble /...call it rap..... tattoo your face.....now your cool
aaronfriedland: I wanna trade you
vtcN_: red neck > white claw
knilecrack: ahahaha
cogforkd: your thoughs on "vitalik buterin"
JeanFrag: that is fake money trading base of streamer popularity
aaronfriedland: I'm up 500,000% on it
httpsdubdubdotcomm: wait i forgot to mention you have to learn the finger gunn blat blat blat while you mumble
JaeGeeTee: Dungeons and Dragons is cool.
cogforkd: HAHA
mutrx: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MJ7R5_BR61I
vtcN_: you should bring back bitconnect
cogforkd: HAHAhis IDEA
thezilion: @georgehotz how to buy drugs in internet? Kappa
yaus_baus: george hotz type beat
veomx: :DDDD
knilecrack: did you watch when snoop immitates mumble rappers?
httpsdubdubdotcomm: ^ no but imma check it
mutrx: watch unusual videos https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MJ7R5_BR61I
aaronfriedland: understanding ewhoring https://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/8806721
mutrx: HAHHA
veomx: gucci mane
mutrx: HDL
chancechants: mcretHahaa
mutrx: HODL
mutrx: what was ur worst investment other than playing around with a play station
aaronfriedland: basically selling other people's nudes to tinder dipshits
mikey9988: monkaW
vtcN_: you ever see the april fools rfc's that ietf does?
ArcherCreatlol: what happened to your ctf stream?
aaronfriedland: @georgehotz https://arxiv.org/pdf/1905.04576.pdf
aaronfriedland: there's the pdf
OnlyB1ade: ...
aaronfriedland: market saturated
httpsdubdubdotcomm: ^
OnlyB1ade: data driven
bytebacon: https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-big-to-small-multi-scale-local-planar#code
mutrx: this has been a fun stream
yaus_baus: thanks
ArcherCreatlol: :(
cogforkd: NOOOOOOOOOOOO
veomx: thanks bro
knilecrack: stream more
JaeGeeTee: NOOOOOO
knilecrack: getbored more often
MrMcaustin1: :)
JaeGeeTee: dont leave us
aaronfriedland: good night
JaeGeeTee: we bored
cogforkd: DONT LEAVE MEEEE
JaeGeeTee: WE SO BORED
cogforkd: :(
Rezii27: Have a good night!
mutrx: react to more reddits and youtubes
Rezii27: Get some rest dude.
JaeGeeTee: ME SO BORED
knilecrack: bb
yaus_baus: bye
ArcherCreatlol: BB
cogforkd: GOOD NIGHT
MrMcaustin1: OBS broke cant end the stream
3ygun: bye
hildl0rdi: bye
thezilion: bye
picklesareok: good stream bye
roystang: goodbye iphone hacker
Mabaet: Bye George!
JaeGeeTee: SAVE THE INTERNET
lek0cs: no doubt NordVOn will slonsor
MrMcaustin1: gn george
cogforkd: TAKECARE
aaronfriedland: *opens incognito window*
anirudhrautela: Goodnight